Are you really going to cut it?
What? You said that you wanted it cut.
You said that drying it is a pain.
I did, but...
You said that it's hot and muggy out,
and that this would make a good summer memory.
I'm sure I didn't say that.
He wasn't asking you to cut it.
Relax your shoulders.
Don't be so uptight, Shun-chan.
Actually, seeing you guys more relaxed than I am makes me nervous.
Let's begin.
I look forward to working with you.
Um, I appreciate the thought,
but just cut it a little bit, please.
Wait a minute!
Are you both cutting my hair?
Don't worry. We have two pairs of scissors...
...but our heart is one.
Are you sure you're not cutting too much, Yuutan?
This side's shorter now.
You're not one at all!
You should do it my way.
Can't we do it my way for once?
Please don't cut and talk at the same time!
It's hot out.
Since it's so hot, let's just cut it all off!
Ah, but, I don't want it all off...
Oh, that's a nice, summery style.
Cut more off! Cut it off!
Um, summer's almost over.
Actually, you can just stop now.
Don't hold back.
This'll look good.
No, it won't!
Careful! Stop moving!
There's no way they're going to listen to you.
In the unyielding sweltering heat,
our short summer was coming to an end.
Oh.
"Oh?" What do you mean by "oh"?!
It's best if you just disregard that.
Yuuki, you...
What is it?!
You shouldn't worry about it.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
mattezu ni toozaketeita no wa atashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta kedo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
Jeez, I told you to only cut a little bit off.
If my hair's too short, it'll frizz like crazy.
Sheesh.
Come in.
Oh, thanks for having us over!
Hello.
My my, you really took a leap, didn't you?
You haven't looked like that since middle school.
Shun-chan, you kept your hair short till middle school?
Ah, yes,
but it was really curly back then too.
I bet you were one cute middle-schooler, Shun-chan.
Is your summer homework coming along well?
Of course, since we have Kaname-kun's notes--
Y-Yes, Kaname-kun's a fantastic teacher.
Oh, my.
I taught him subtraction when he was little,
and now he's become the teacher.
Isn't that right, Kaname-sensei?
You're the only one who calls me that.
Don't you need to go shopping for dinner?
Would you like to come with me, Kaname-kun?
No!
Can't you see that I'm studying?
You used to come with me.
What's more important, your mother or your studies?
Hey, didn't you hear her?
What's more important, her or your work?
You can study 'till your eyes bleed, but it won't make a difference if you don't understand girls, Kanamecchi.
She's not a girl! She's my mother!
Fine.
I can tell your studies are more important to you than your own mother.
You made her cry.
You shouldn't make girls cry!
Shut up!
Just get out of here, Mom!
You're in the way!
Sorry.
Oh, how pitiful.
What are you doing?
Chase after her and tell her you're sorry!
It could be the beginning of a beautiful relationship!
She wants you to chase her. Can't you see that?
Enough already!
This watermelon's delicious.
I can't understand why you would ever put salt on something so delicious!
I prefer eating them as they are, too.
I wonder why people put salt on watermelon...
The salt makes the watermelon seem even sweeter, doesn't it?
And absence makes the heart grow fonder, doesn't it?
No, it doesn't.
I guess I could put salt on it if I got tired of the flavor.
Yeah. Kaname, when you and your mother get tired of living together...
Add salt.
No way!
Finish your food and do your work!
Thanks for the food!
All right!
I feel like I'm smarter now!
I can do it!
I know I can do it now!
Illness starts in the mind,
and studying starts with glasses.
Kanamecchi, do you want some?
Wait, you already have a pair! I'm so stupid!
I already told you...
If you have time to play with cheap glasses, you might as well do some homework!
100 yen stores have everything.
Memorization set.
Victory headband.
Stress ball.
AnPanda Ball
Squeezing it stimulates your brain.
They really do have everything.
Why did you buy all this unnecessary stuff for studying?
It kinda just happened.
Kanamecchi, how long have you been wearing glasses?
Yeah, how long has it been?
Forget about that and study—
You didn't have them in kindergarten.
You were already looking at the world through dark-colored glasses, though.
There was that one rainy day, when we were making teru-teru bouzu dolls...
I bet you'll draw weird faces on yours.
You're so mean.
You're viewing us through dark-colored glasses.
That's called prejudice.
That wasn't prejudicial at all.
In any case, you've been wearing glasses since you were born.
Don't say that!
Man, that's awful.
You're childhood friends, but you forgot when Kanamecchi changed his image.
We didn't forget. We never remembered it in the first place.
That's nothing to be proud of.
Didn't you start wearing glasses in the second year of middle school?
Second year?
No, that was...
Tsukahara-kun.
Aren't these yours?
Oh, thank you.
I can't believe you lost them so soon after entering middle school.
You should wear them all the time, don't you think?
Yeah, but...
He definitely has coke-bottle glasses.
Let's call him a nerd next time we see him!
Yeah, they don't look cool.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I lost again.
Yuuki-kun, you're too good at thumb wrestling.
You're just too weak, Shun.
Shall I take you on left-handed?
If you use your left hand,
Shun will have to use his left hand, too.
Oh, you're right.
What are you doing?
Ah, Kaname-kun.
Thumb wrestling in middle school?
You must have nothing to do.
If you have time for that,
let's go check out some clubs.
We need to decide soon.
But thumb wrestling is fun!
Here, look at this. Yuuki-kun drew my face!
Isn't it cute?
This is mine.
He's saying, "I can beat you even while reading manga."
That's right. Yuuki's really good at thumb wrestling.
That's great.
I don't think it'll play much of a role in our middle school lives, though.
Kaname, have your eyes gotten worse?
Huh?
Um, a little.
What?! Really? So that means you can't see the board...
Well, I'll wear glasses during class.
Glasses?
Kaname-kun, you got glasses?
Show us how you look in them.
I wanna see, I wanna see!
Are those your glasses? Is that the case?
Hey, hands off!
I'll never wear them in front of you guys.
You'll laugh at me.
Shun's not like that.
I'm talking about you two!
I'm sure you'll call me "Nerd" or "Four-eyes."
We wouldn't say that.
Or would we?
Why can't you give a clear answer?
Then why don't you thumb wrestle me, Kaname?
If I win, you'll show us what you look like with your glasses on.
What?
Why would I--
Sounds good.
Hey!
Oh, I'm so excited.
Why'd you answer for me?!
It's decided.
Kaname, I'll draw a face on your thumb, too.
I don't need one!
Stop it!
Come on, hold still.
If you move, your face will be weird.
It's weird enough already.
Matsuoka-kun.
Yes?
What are you doing?
It looks fun!
We're thumb wrestling.
Thumb wrestling?
Drawing your face on your thumb is like a traditional part of thumb wrestling.
See?
How cute!
This, too?
That's right.
Yuuta-kun, do you like drawing?
What?
Are you joining the Art Club?
We haven't decided what club we're joining yet.
The Art Club wouldn't be bad.
Ah, but the upperclassmen in
the Volleyball Club saw Yuuta-kun during PE,
and said they wanted tall guys like him.
That's Yuuki.
What?
That's Yuuki,
and I'm Yuuta.
I-I'm so sorry!
That was embarrassing!
We got them confused!
People get the two of you mixed up a lot.
But they're both so good looking.
They really do look alike.
Well, we're exactly the same, aside from our bangs.
They're identical.
Should I make the eyebrows thicker?
Do you want round glasses?
Silver frames?
Coke-bottles?
What do you mean it's just your bangs? You two are completely different!
You piss me off way more than he does!
You And I
East, Asaba Shoryu.
West, Tsukahara.
I don't get a title?
Face each other... Ready...
Begin!
Amazing. What a match!
Kaname's pretty good.
You think you can beat me while reading manga?
I've got this one in the bag!
Watch it!
It wasn't on purpose.
My hand slipped.
Hey, ref!
He just violated the rules!
You'll have to put your glasses on to protect your eyes, it seems.
Yes.
Why?!
Just punish him!
Okay, okay.
Yuuki, if you foul three times, you lose.
Three's plenty.
He only has two eyes.
Kaname-kun, calm down!
Start over.
Play fair this time.
Fine, fine.
Ready, fight!
Look at that!
I've never seen such thumb wrestling.
That wasn't a foul. That was a ten-don.
A what? That doesn't even make sense!
It's gone way beyond thumb wrestling now.
This sucks.
What?
Are you resigning because you're afraid you'll lose?
Just let us see what your glasses look like.
You... Wait!
Stop!
I'll just take a peek.
Ow.
That hurt.
Apologize, first year.
Oh, the glasses.
Hey!
Sorry.
There, there.
I can't believe first years these days.
Glasses, glasses.
What are you doing, Yuuki? You have to apologize.
If you keep acting like that,
they'll have it in for you.
"Have it in for him"?
You know...
Some older punks will get underclassmen to meet them behind the gym
and then, they'll beat up the underclassmen.
It happens all the time in manga.
Really? That's so scary!
You'll be fine, Shun.
They might ask you to meet them there for other reasons, though.
Don't do anything dangerous, Yuuki-kun.
Me?
I'll be fine.
Even if something happens,
maybe they'll let me settle it peacefully... with a thumb wrestling match.
As if you'd settle something peacefully.
It's oil-based ink.
One day, Yuuki will get what's coming to him.
Hey, Yuuki...
Is he in there? I can't see.
Hey, do you know...
where Yuuki Asaba is?
Asaba-kun?
I just saw Asaba-kun heading towards the gym with some third years.
Third years?
Can't be...
But...
He's going to the gym with some upperclassmen.
This could be...
This could be bad!
It's his own fault that he doesn't have any manners.
It serves him right. Right.
Yuuta! Shun!
Kaname-kun, what's wrong?
Yuuki was...
Yuuki was dragged off behind the gym!
What?
It's probably because he refused to apologize when he bumped into them yesterday.
Let's go to the gym and...
No, it's fine.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you worried?
If we don't do something, Yuuki's gonna get beat up by some third years!
Can you call yourself Yuuki's...
Well, we don't know if he's been beaten up yet.
Just stand up. Come on.
Huh? What are you all doing?
Like I said, Yuuki's gonna...
Huh?
Yuu... ta?
Yeah.
Huh?
Some guys from the Volleyball Club forced me to go to the gym to watch them play.
It was a hassle, but I went anyway.
Why...?
The gym? Then...
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I win, Kaname-kun.
So, what happened to Yuuki?
Nothing, nothing, nothing at all!
Shun, you should have told me!
I was going to, but you seemed so desperate.
I wasn't...
Yuuta, what am I going to do?
Kaname was so worried about—
Don't say it!
Kaname-kun, are those...
I know you lost at thumb wrestling,
but I didn't think you'd actually wear them.
Nothing good comes from not being able to see.
Not bad. They look good on you.
Why does that sound condescending coming from you?
Hey! What are you drawing?
They really do look good on you.
You don't have to say that.
Kaname-kun, you look really good in glasses.
Finished.
You used oil-based ink again!
Who cares?
You'll be wearing glasses from now on,
Kaname-lens-kun.
What's Kaname-lens?!
Whoops, I remembered something I shouldn't have.
I'll carry that shame to my grave.
So, how long have you had glasses?
Since second year of middle school?
Yeah, my second year of middle school.
Wasn't it our first year...
Kaname-lens-kun?
What? What's a Kaname-lens-kun?
You...
Well, Kaname was really worried about me...
Don't say it!
Masaki-chan!
Do I look weird?
...suits you.
Huh?
It really suits you!
Really? That's good.
Sorry.
You Have One New Message
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
It's from Chizuru-kun.
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
I got my hair cut in the garden at Kaname-kun's house.
Really?
I got my hair cut, but it didn't help with the heat as much as I expected.
Shall we go?
Yeah!
Among the sunset's clouds and occasional breeze,
I could feel the summer ending.
Glasses and Et cetera
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Giving me the chance to answer you and the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta n dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto mo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you and me both
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
"Next time: Next to an Apple."
Next to an Apple