Welcome.
That'll be 420 yen.
Thank you very much.
She probably seemed familiar because her hair looked...
a little like this, curling under my finger.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
There's nothing to do.
There's always nothing to do.
This is different. Very different!
Don't you remember how we shone doing this and that at the cultural festival?
Suddenly going back to our ordinary lives is boring.
Yeah.
And there's nothing to do during class, either.
Well, shouldn't you be paying attention to class during class?
Anyhow, let's have lunch.
I'm so hungry.
Seriously?
Huh? What?
Wet Paint
Do Not
Enter
Cafeteria-Store
Making my big debut in the famous school cafeteria!
It's been a while since we last came here.
There are some free seats over there.
Well, we did come all the way down here, after all.
Udon
Soba
Yam
udon/soba
Seaweed
Tanuki
udon/soba
Tempura
Kitsune
udon/soba
Ramen
Miso Ramen
Shio Ramen
Pork Ramen
Saury
noodles
Curry
Curry Pork
Katsudon
Oyakodon
Chinese
Rice Bowl
Stamina
Bowl
Daily
Special A
Special B
Vegetable
udon/soba
So cheap!
Udon for 250 yen!
They have more on the menu than I expected.
All right!
I'm gonna conquer everything on their menu!
That might be difficult.
They have daily specials.
It's different every day.
What? Then I'll have to come here every day!
That's right. This day will never come again.
Tempura udon/soba
Ramen
Complete domination of the menu is easier said than done!
Get out of the way.
What are you doing, Kanamecchi?
It's your fault for just standing there.
As if I'll let you get in front of me!
The first one to order shall be me, Chizu—
Achoo.
H-Hey! Come on, Yukki! What was that for?
Sorry. Just caught a little cold.
Cough, cough.
Next.
Um, kitsune udon, large size.
You're not sick at all!
Miso Ramen
Damn it.
That cheater.
Shun-chan!
Over here.
What is it?
Cinderella's working in the cafeteria!
You're right. She's beautiful.
I know, right?
Yukki!
Yukki, look! Over here!
Yeah, yeah, I saw.
What's wrong with you? You're no fun.
Well, that's how it is mostly. Yuuki-kun's not all that interested in his surroundings.
Excuse me...
Yes?
I thought I ordered kitsune udon...
What?
Oh my, it completely slipped my mind. I'm sorry!
You're welcome to have the tempura, too, if you'd like.
But...
Oh, it's fine, take it. Just think of it as a token of my love for you.
If only I were twenty years younger...
You're making it harder to take it.
Everyone, there's a cougar-killer over here!
With its warm food and a beautiful Cinderella,
the cafeteria's a pretty great place.
It's getting cold up on the roof.
Why don't we eat inside for a while?
Good idea.
I agree!
What?
Someone's not happy with your idea.
I won't be able to collect the stickers if we eat here every day.
Stickers?
Yeah, from the convenience store.
If I collect thirty points from buying bread, I get a plate.
You only have nine points.
That's what I mean...
I'll never get enough if we eat here every day.
Why don't you bring your convenience store bread here?
That won't work. Watching all of you eat cafeteria food...
would make me want some, too.
He can be quite a handful sometimes...
I got it, I got it! I'll help you!
Let's all help Yukki collect stickers!
You shouldn't say such things if you don't really intend to do them.
I want to shine, as if I were reliving the festival!
Sure, but how?
Why don't we rotate who eats the bread each day...
and give all the stickers to Yukki?
We'll call it "Sticker Duty!"
How ground-breaking.
I'll help.
It's decided! Let's start tomorrow.
Who'll go first?
Me, me, me! I'll do it!
Why won't you give me any extra?
We don't hand out freebies.
That's a lie.
I saw you give someone tempura and fried tofu.
Is he talking about the mix up with Yuuki's udon?
Cinderella's in trouble!
Go help her out.
Why?
Don't say that. Hurry up!
Cinderella's a delicate girl who can't stand up for herself!
And she's still waiting for her prince to ride up on his white horse!
Wait, you're going?!
Come on. We're growing boys.
If you give us something extra, we'll take you to the movies—
Enough.
What?
You think I'd want to go to a movie with little boys who make a fuss over extra food?
You should learn to support yourselves...
before you even think about asking out a girl.
Cinderella was amazing at lunch.
She really shut them up.
You just grabbed a towel and came back,
since there was nothing for you to do, Chizuru.
Tsk.
Shut up!
It just means I'll only be a prince for my one true love!
Your one true love?
Never mind, never mind.
Cafeteria-Store
Excuse me!
Yes, thanks for waiting.
Oh!
Thanks for lunch.
You run the store?
Yes. Sorry, but we're about to eat lunch.
Did you need something?
Yukki, she's asking you what you want.
Oh, that.
Can I have that, please?
That?
That, please.
Silly boy!
My daughter is-not-for-sale!
Wh-What were you th-thinking?!
There's an order to these things!
You start with something like an exchange diary!
That's not what I meant.
Kayo, Kayo! Come here!
What is it, Mother?
This kid's got business with you!
What?
Um, I was wondering if I could have that...
It's half-eaten.
I mean the bag.
The bag? Sure.
Actually, I wanted the sticker.
The sticker? I can't give you that.
Just give him the sticker, Kayo!
I'm collecting them. He can't have it.
Can't you make an exception?
Come on!
He's really desperate!
How do you figure that?
Collect them yourself instead of taking them from others.
But I need to collect thirty points' worth, and it's difficult.
So does everyone else!
Who cares about one little plate?
You already have some, you know!
I gave you the Yamawaki bread plates.
Don't say that in front of them!
You're embarrassing me!
I'm the one who's embarrassed!
The daughter I've raised as a single mother won't even give someone a measly sticker!
That has nothing to do with stickers!
Why are you so stubborn?
Do you know how hard I've worked to collect these stickers?
I'm so embarrassed that my face is on fire.
I'll never give it away.
You And I
Oh, sorry.
You really are collecting stickers.
You're the girl from the store.
You came to buy bread, didn't you?
Extremely delicious.
Juicy Sausage
I don't need to buy bread every day,
because we're starting Sticker Duty,
but I'll get points faster if I buy bread as well,
so I'm not sure what to do.
What's Sticker Duty?
Are you sleepy?
No, I'm fine.
I see.
It's unusual for a high school boy to want a plate.
You're into this sort of thing?
Bread Festival
Anpanda
The Brave Plate
I guess.
Hm...
I'm collecting stickers because I like them, too.
Do you read anime magazines?
Huh? What magazines?
Guess not.
What magazines?
Nothing.
Hey, how many points do you have?
What's so funny?
Sorry. It's just cute that you've got only got one point stickers on your sheet.
So many two's and three's... and a four.
A student can't afford a bread worth four points.
Just goes to show what a working adult with a salary can do.
Did the four point sticker come from the extra large yakisoba bread?
Wh-Why does that matter?
I've just wanted to try it for a while.
Did you finish it all?
Why do you care?
Are you sure?
I've gotta go.
It's fine. No one will know.
I guess I don't have to get one today.
Huh?
Red Bean Bread
This one doesn't have a sticker.
Wait!
You girls...
You took the sticker off this bread, didn't you?
What?
Don't give me "what". The sticker.
You can't take the stickers without buying the bread!
Hand it over.
Kids these days...
Huh? Where'd he go?
Why'd you run away?
No one screams about stickers in a store.
I'm pretending I don't know you.
Wh-What's with that?
I didn't yell because I wanted to!
Are you saying you don't care...
if people take stickers without buying the bread?
I do care.
See?
What a ridiculous morning.
What?
Nothing.
You should get to school.
You'll be late.
Right...
Huh? Yukki.
You're up early.
I'm on Sticker Duty today,
so I thought I'd buy it before school.
Then, I recommend the extra large yakisoba bread.
What's that?
Can't you enjoy your food more?
You're making mine taste worse.
But it's so hard!
Chizuru, don't you usually put away two slices of bread easily?
It's mentally challenging!
You're all eating cafeteria food,
and I have to eat convenience store bread.
I feel left out.
What are you saying?
You're the one who came up with Sticker Duty.
It's your own fault.
No, it's your fault to begin with.
It's fine! Just wave your delicious food in my face while you're eating it.
Ah, this bread's so good!
Ah, Chizuru-kun, take this.
Thanks! You're the only one who's always nice to me, Shun-chan.
Don't baby him, Shun.
He'll never learn if you keep that up.
What did you say?
Since you're always mean to me, take this!
What do you think you're eating?
You won't miss one.
Besides, it's not even that good.
Then spit it out! Come on!
Stop it! You'll make me drool out the juice!
Sounds like it's delicious!
Not true!
Quiet down.
You bonehead! Spit it out!
What's wrong with them enjoying their meal?
Spit it out!
You're too nice to them.
Isn't it nice to see them getting along?
They're that loud because they're obviously not getting along.
Shun-chan!
Masaki-chan.
I'm surprised you knew we'd be here.
I figured you'd be here since they blocked off the roof.
S-Sorry. Looks like you're not done eating.
That's okay.
Do you need help with your homework?
What are you having trouble with?
This one.
I had trouble with this one, too.
You did?
Yes. You should start by solving this bit here.
Oh, I see.
What's wrong with you?! Don't get in the way!
I don't even care.
I'll just eat the food Shun-chan gave me.
Huh? It won't come out.
What's wrong with this thing?
Damn it. There!
Boys' Bathroom
Sorry, Shun-chan.
It's okay.
Class is starting.
If it doesn't get washed off now, it'll stain!
Thank you.
Well, I'm the one who got it on you.
Hey...
Yes?
Shun-chan, do you not have one?
Not have what?
Well... as in...
someone you like?
I mean...
I just thought it'd be nice to talk about stuff we don't usually discuss!
Someone I like?
Not at the moment, I guess.
I see.
Chizuru-kun, what about you?
What? M-Me?
F-For me, w-well...
it's Shun-chan!
I'm falling, Chizuru-kun!
I hope your uniform doesn't stain.
It's fine.
I wonder about everyone else, though.
Wonder about what?
If there's anyone they like.
Wet Paint
Do Not
Enter
Oh, it's you!
Good timing! Could you wipe some tables down for me?
I came to buy a notebook.
I cut my finger.
See?
I can't leave until I finish this, so I want your help.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Hey.
Want some stickers?
How many points will you give me?
Don't wipe them like that!
Don't push the crumbs from the table onto the floor!
We'll have to sweep the floor again!
This better be worth at least three points.
There you go again! How many times is that?
Hey, what are you going to do with the plate?
Are you going to eat curry rice on it?
I don't think I'd eat curry on it.
Huh?
The plate would probably turn yellow.
I probably won't use it for anything else, either.
What? You were listening?
I'm listening.
You're right.
Even if you get the plate, you can't use it.
The art's too cute!
But my mom doesn't get it all,
so she always tries to use it.
I see.
It's getting dark.
Pick up the pace. I need to go soon.
Are you going somewhere?
No, we just eat dinner early.
My mom goes to bed early.
You go straight home to eat dinner?
It's just my mom and me at home.
I don't want to make my mom eat alone.
She just watches TV when I'm not there, though.
Are you finished? Good work.
Thanks for the help.
What about my sticker?
Oh, I forgot.
Again...
Udon
Soba
Yam
udon/soba
Seaweed
Tanuki
udon/soba
Tempura
Kitsune
udon/soba
Ramen
Miso Ramen
Shio Ramen
Pork Ramen
Saury
noodles
Curry
Curry Pork
Katsudon
Oyakodon
Chinese
Rice Bowl
Stamina
Bowl
Daily
Special A
Special B
Vegetable
udon/soba
It won't come off. Sorry.
Try a little harder.
So you got one point.
That's great.
That was definitely three points' worth of work.
Is this the sticker she gave you?
Yeah, that's it.
She must be a really nice girl to give you a sticker when she's collecting them, too.
She's pretty, too.
Pretty...
No, she's not pretty.
Really?
Yeah.
Plate Giveaway
Plate Givea way
Point
It looked a little like this, curling under my finger.
The next time I saw that hair was behind my eyelids.
What should I eat at the cafeteria today?
Yuuki, aren't you on Sticker Duty today?
What? No way.
Crescent Moon Silhouette
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Giving me the chance to answer the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
Next time: Middle School Diary
Middle School Diary