Good morning.
Hey, for today...
Yeah?
We need an afro, joke glasses... and what else?
Were you up late last night?
Yeah, I couldn't figure out how to allocate
the cultural festival budget for our class.
I was up all night thinking it over.
You must be busy as both a class rep and a member of the student council.
It's even worse with the festival coming u—
Shun-chan, Kanamecchi!
Good mammaring!
So Shun, what's your class doing?
Oh, my class is...
H-Hey, don't ignore me!
You're supposed to say hello!
They responded to that correctly.
Yup.
I don't believe you two!
Um, Chizuru-kun...
Ignore him. There's no point in even replying.
So Shun, what's your class doing?
We're doing a café with a twist.
Yeah, everyone's gonna cross-dress.
Cross-dress?
Really? Awesome!
Kaname-kun, what's your class doing?
A stereotypical haunted house.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
There isn't much time 'til the festival.
Use this extended homeroom period effectively and work on your projects.
That is all.
With the cultural festival approaching, the classroom
is overflowing with irrepressible anticipation...
comforting bustle...
and trouble.
Hey, Tsukahara-kun.
What do you think of advertising by walking around the school
in our haunted house costumes with placards?
Doesn't that sound interesting?
What?
We're already pushing the budget.
We don't need to do that.
We're making posters.
What? But the flashier it is, the more people we'll attract!
That's right.
Well, Tsukahara-kun?
Well, I'll see if we can shift some money from somewhere else.
Great!
Thanks!
What should we do?
What about a kappa?
That sounds good, doesn't it?
Budget Recalculation
Hey, Tsukahara.
How do I go about getting blackout curtains from the school?
What? You haven't gotten any yet?
If you don't hurry,
someone else will get to them before us!
Sorry, sorry.
So, how do I get them?
Go to the Student Council Office,
get an equipment request form and fill out...
That's too much work.
It's more work for me to keep on explaining it to you!
Tsukahara-kun, do you have a minute?
It's about assigning roles on the day of the festival.
Could you look at this?
Oh, this is...
Hold on, Tsukahara.
What about the curtains?
Tsu-ka-ha-ra!
Fine! I'll do it!
Really?
Budget Recalculation
Blackout
Man, you're the greatest!
Shut up.
Damn, it's always this, that or the other.
I guess we'll decide roles later.
Yeah, thanks.
Hey, Yuuki and that monkey—I mean, Tachibana... where'd they go?
Yuu-ta.
Shun-chan.
What are you doing? Don't you have homeroom, too?
There's something I want to show you two.
Ta-da!
Yukki and I made them!
Our environmentally-friendly eco-trains!
Half of the train is made out of kindness.
Are you using that in your haunted house?
What? No.
They made it even though they won't use it...
Even though everyone's busy with preparations...
Get in, Yuuta. I'll pull you.
But we're in the middle of preparations.
All right then, your big brother will ride it.
Okay, Yuuki-kun?
Mandarins
How is it, sir?
You look safe and snug in that box!
Really?
But it feels more like I'm trapped in a box...
Where would you like to go, sir?
We can go anywhere.
Straying off the beaten path is our motto.
Whose lazy son are you?
Please take us to Azuma-sensei.
There's something I want to borrow from him.
Roger.
The eco-train is departing.
That's not fair!
Damn it!
I can't believe you installed a bottomless feature!
I was caught off guard!
Since when did cardboard boxes become so high-tech?
Sir, please entrust me with your life!
What?
Speed up!
U-Um...
Curve!
And we've arrived.
Uh, um... Chizuru-kun...
What's with th—
The sweat? Don't worry about it.
Not the sweat.
What's that?
Please don't worry about it.
More importantly, I had something to ask...
What was it?
Azuma-sensei.
Um, I want to borrow some materials...
Another one? Is this a new fad?
I'm not sure.
Yukki, you cheater!
I won't lose next time!
I've installed my own bottomless feature!
That's just broken, isn't it?
Will this do?
Alice in Wonderland
Yes, thank you.
How are your preparations for the festival coming along?
I trust it's going well?
Yes.
People from outside the school will be coming for the festival,
so do your best.
Azuma-sensei, bring your girlfriend to the festival!
What?
Unfortunately... I don't have a girlfriend at the moment.
What a surprise.
I figured you'd be popular.
You're so kind and handsome, after all.
Maybe he doesn't want to settle on just one!
He goes through girls like pages of a daily calendar.
That's not it.
Well, you know how girls act all cutesy and energetic?
I've never been able to deal with it very well.
Really?
He's always been popular...
So, where's Tsukahara-kun?
Kanamecchi is...
What about me?
Huh?
Yuuki, Monkey...
What are you doing, huh?
Kanamecchi!
Huh? W-Wait— Yukki!
Don't you realize we don't have time for this?
Ow!
Why just me?
Jeez. The extended homeroom period ended and you guys have done nothing.
Shun and Yuuta, head back to your classroom.
You left the class rep in the lurch.
Oh, right. We were in the middle of making flowers.
You two, as well.
Yeah, yeah.
They're hard work, aren't they?
It's nothing new.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I'm not...
You And I
Matsuoka-kun, Asaba-kun!
Which costume do you want to wear at the festival?
They're all so cute. I don't know which to choose.
You can't choose?
What?
I'm sure you two would look good in anything!
Yeah!
Really?
Cheshire!
I bet they'd look good in these, too!
What?
Yukki.
This will be our first time...
Our first time...
Chizuru-san...
You know, you're not in middle school any more.
Stop getting giddy every time someone says it's their first time.
You're just using the copier for the first time.
Sowwie, sowwie.
Yukki, have you used a copier before?
It's my first time, too.
Yukki, it's your first time, too!
Your first... first time...
Starting copying.
Start
Stop
Divide
Reset
Huh? It's blank?!
I think it's trying to throw us off by not spitting out copies easily.
Sorry, can I skip ahead of you?
I'm in a hurry.
Go ahead.
Ah, so that's how you do it...
2—4 Cultural Festival
•List of different work groups
Costume making group
Meeting hall prep group
Receiving group
Ghost volunteer group
Prop creating group
Tour guide group
•Types of creatures
Sadako
Toilet ghost Hanako
Lantern demon
Jason
Zombies
Ghosts
Other major monsters
Jiang Shi vampire
•Necessary equipment
Blackout curtains
Place the original face down!
I'll be copying that technique!
Don't you feel like we're getting better at making copies...
because we're copying others?
Spot on.
As experts at copying, we'll get it right this time—
Huh?
2—4 Cultural
•List of different work groups
Costume making group
Meeting hall prep group
Receiving group
•Types of creatures
Sadako
Toilet ghost Hanako
Lantern demon
Gho
Pro
Tou
Zombies
Ghosts
Other m
What is this?
Hey look, they keep coming!
Sorry.
Kaname asked for eight sheets, so I pressed eight.
What?!
How do we stop this thing?
Hey, stop! Stop!
Good...
It's not good. Look.
We made eight wasteful, failed copies.
How terrible for the planet.
What's wrong with this thing?
Technology is meant to be making our lives easier!
Oh, I know the reason. It must be because technology advances so quickly that humans can't keep up.
It won't be long before robots turn against humans.
That actually might be possible.
What are you, stupid?
Kaname.
I only asked for eight copies.
Why are you wasting so much time on this?
Wow, Kanamecchi! You're brilliant!
And you're brilliant... at being stupid.
There you are!
We're asking people what role they want to have during the festival.
We'll be right there!
Tsukahara-senpai! Good timing!
Senpai! Three classes want to use the home economics classroom on the day of the festival.
Their reps are arguing about it in the Student Council Office right now.
What?
Senpai, do something!
Do something?
Kaname, aren't you coming?
Huh? Um...
Senpai, hurry up!
Okay, I'm coming.
Yuuki, you know that name-thing...
I mean, the place where you...
Huh?
Huh? What?
Reception! The reception desk!
Put my name down for that!
Reception? Boring.
More like, he's stumbling over his words...
Hey, Princess.
What are you doing?
We're getting fitted for our outfits for the festival.
We're waiting to be tacked.
Yuuki! Monkey! Where are you?
Uh-oh, it's Kanamecchi!
Didn't take him long to notice.
Did you do something to make him mad again?
Um...
Can you hide us for a bit?
What?
Damn it, where'd they go?
Shun, Yuuta, have you seen Yuuki and the monkey?
Nope.
N-N-No, is something wrong?
I said I wanted to work at reception during the festival,
but I'm signed up to be a ghost.
I know they did it.
Hey, you guys look rather fetching.
What are those? Your outfits for...
Sorry!
Hey.
Let me look under your skirt.
What?
Just flip it up already!
D-Don't do...
Just let me see!
Hey, you can't!
Why not?
Oh my, Kaname-san, what a bold pervert you are.
What? That's not what I'm doing!
You think I'd enjoy looking up his skirt?
What do you mean?
There might be a strange world unknown to you under there.
What are trying to say?!
Are you stupid?
Nice one, Yuutan!
Keep distracting him!
Hey, don't start imagining weird things!
I'm wearing a jersey under here!
Then...
You shouldn't have any problems with letting me take a look!
Just let me look!
No!
Enough already...
Y-You pervert.
Um... this isn't...!
Awful! You're awful!
How dare you! How dare you do that to Shun-chan!
You've got the wrong...
Hey! You guys aren't getting away!
You've been awfully cranky lately.
Well, being cranky is practically a hobby for him.
Just whose fault do you think that is?
Kaname, can you make enlarged copies?
Huh? Why?
The Manga Society asked me to do this huge favor and make enlarged copies of their advertisement posters,
but I don't really want to.
You do it.
I can't believe you're asking me for favors after I got mad at you.
Fine.
I suppose I'll have to help, considering how bad—
Tsukahara!
We need you for a moment.
Something terrible happened.
Sure.
Can your copies wait? I have to...
Huh? Sure.
Tsukahara, this way. Hurry!
Okay.
—
Budget Recalculation
Blackout curtains
What is this? Blackout curtains?
Blackout—
Blackout curtains?
There aren't any left.
N-None?
No.
Not a single one?
N-No.
S-Senpai?
Your class is putting on a haunted house?
That will need tons of curtains.
You should've turned in your request sooner...
Senpai?
You're right.
We're running a haunted house. Right.
"I'm right?"
You'll have to change it into something simple to prepare, or...
That won't be easy.
Yeah, but...
It's okay.
A bunch of classes took extra just in case they needed them.
You should have enough if you borrow some from them.
I see.
You're right.
Blackout curtains
15 sheets
Number of items :
Purpose:
To use in the haunted house
for the cultural festival
Note:
Teacher Seal of Approval
Your request has been approved.
Here.
Approved
Good luck with your haunted house.
Thanks.
We're almost done with props...
All the roles have been decided...
Where are the curtains?
Tsukahara, what happened with the curtains?
Huh? Yeah, I got some.
Oh, thanks a lot, man!
You shouldn't make others do your work for you!
So what? Tsukahara's more reliable than me.
You're useless!
You're so mean.
Budget Recalculation
Blackout curtains
Hey, hey, Shun-chan, I'm gonna be a ghost.
What kind do you think I should be?
Let's see...
How do you feel about a spandex bodysuit?
A spandex bodysuit?
Yes.
Why would I wear that?
Yuuki, is the Manga Society doing anything for the festival?
A manga café.
Apparently, they do it every year.
I see.
Yuuki, I haven't copied the posters for the Manga Society yet.
Can it wait until tomorrow?
Huh? Forget about it.
I already did it.
Well, Yuuta did it for me.
Yuuta said he knew how to make enlarged copies, too.
I might as well have him do it if I'm asking you.
What does that mean?
You're working so hard, I wasn't sure you could fit it in.
I reckoned it'd only turn out well by sheer luck.
Yeah, you're so unreliable.
I know what you mean.
Kanamecchi? Is something wrong?
I get it!
Ow! Why only me?
Don't fight before the festival.
The days leading up to the festival were like a storm.
If I lost focus for a minute, I'd be swept away.
Kaname-kun, don't be angry...
But if I got swept away, I'd see a change of scenery.
Now you've done it!
Just wait until you see what kind of ghost I'll make you be!
Bring it on!
I'll use my Student Council influence to make you perform
a Hyottoko dance all by yourself at the festival.
What? You can't do that!
Kaname, that's an obvious abuse of power...
Of course it is. Power's no good if you don't use it.
Shun-chan, Kanamecchi's being mean!
Careful, Chizuru-kun!
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Giving me the chance to answer the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
Next time: On your mark.