Autumn clouds float high in the blue sky.
Having had our fill of eating,
reading manga, and playing sports this summer,
we celebrated the arts this fall.
You want me to draw a manga?
Y-Yes. Twice a year, the Manga Society...
creates an anthology out of manga we've drawn.
Really?
So they do have some club-like activities...
at the Manga Society.
Sorry?
I was enjoying how it was kinda like a do-nothing-and-go-home club.
But even if I agree to draw a manga,
I don't own a beret.
You don't need a beret to draw manga.
I don't own a striped shirt or have an F in the middle of my name either.
You don't need any of those.
Please make your manga at least five pages long.
If you have any questions, just ask.
Um, who are you?
I'm a first year. M-Matsushita Ryuunosuke.
A-Anyway, see what you can do.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
Those look great.
Shun-chan, can I have one?
Go ahead.
Why do you have those?
What are you, a girl?
Can I have one, too?
So...
You're all going to draw a manga for me.
Daily Wage Hero
What? B-But why?
So that's why you called us here?
Yes.
Isn't this your club activity?
We don't have anything to do with it.
Well, yeah, but you know...
I only read manga.
I've never drawn one before.
That's why we'll draw in the relay format.
We'll each draw one page and
combine them to create one story.
Ah, I'll do it!
Sounds interesting, doesn't it?
Yes!
I'll hand out the paper.
I'll pass. I don't draw.
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't say stuff that'll undermine our teamwork
when we're about to start a group project.
We don't have any teamwork to undermine.
What should it be about?
Let's see...
How about a sport-com?
A sports comedy?
Don't you think that'd be hard to draw?
Yeah, it might be difficult for you if you can't even figure out
that "sport-com" means a competitive sports story.
I'd prefer a fantasy story with wizards.
You would.
You're a bit of a fantasy creature, yourself.
Why don't we draw a romantic comedy documenting...
the love between Kaname and his mom?
That wouldn't be a comedy.
It's too taboo.
What if someone spotted them?
"At the Tsukahara family, whom she works for, the mother and son are..."
Enough!
This is getting out of hand.
Why not stick to...
the simple, classic adventure of a hero,
with a demon king and monsters?
A hero...
An adventure...
I see!
We've been forgetting about the all-important genre!
The adventure of an ambitious and brave hero is at the core of our youth!
Okay, let's give it a try!
Well then, first up to bat is Yuutan with the first page!
Yukki will be second!
Shun-chan is third, and I'll go fourth!
And Kanamecchi will draw the fifth and final page!
Isn't this exciting?
Kanamecchi, you'll have to carry our efforts over the finish line...
with an emotional conclusion.
Yeah, I'll carry all of your failures to a pathetically weak finish.
I finished the first page.
Finally!
How does it start?
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
Hey, this is good!
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
I'm a hero!
You are the only one
who can save this world.
Yuuta-kun, I didn't know you could draw!
I don't, but I grew up in a room overflowing to the rafters with Yuuki's manga.
It's only natural that this would happen.
No, it's not.
This is amazing!
Yes!
I swear on this legendary sword!
His costume and sword are awesome!
Hey, who are these two standing next to the hero?
The country's best spearman and a sex-appeal magician.
It's perfect. This is what boys want!
Are you stupid?
What are you trying to say about innocent boys?
But I think it's a great start.
It is, isn't it?
All right! Yukki, keep this going and draw something awesome!
I'm done with the second page.
What?
Who's this? What's up with that outfit?
A convenience store?
Is he going to a convenience store?
What happened between the first and second pages?
Yuuta's costume was too hard to draw.
I simplified it and ended up with this.
What did you simplify to have him turn into this?
You'd have to "simplify" your costs to make such a low budget hero.
The only thing you worked hard on, the sword, looks even more pitiful.
They couldn't be more mismatched.
Huh?
His two friends are missing. Where are they?
They died.
Already?
It took all the effort I had just to draw one character.
Thats why I had them say to him "Overcome my death!"
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
Overcome
my death.
a
This speech bubble doesn't overcome anything!
He's totally crushing them under there.
You're hopeless, Yukki.
Shun-chan, it's up to you now.
O-Okay, I'll do my best!
I'm done with the third page!
The hero's eyes are huge!
In this scene, the hero doesn't give up despite the loss of his friends,
and fixes his gaze on what's ahead.
Well, with those eyes, he's not just looking ahead—he must have 360° vision!
The bitterness of losing his friends to monsters has made made the hero even stronger, it seems.
No, he lost his friends to your artistic skills.
It looks like we've got a new character.
A-Are you the hero?!
Exactly what part of this guy in a t-shirt made him seem like a hero to her?
She probably spotted his sword with those huge eyes of hers.
My sister...
She's been kidnapped by monsters!
Help me, Mister Hero!
My sister... She's been kidnapped by monsters!
My sister...
She's been kidnapped by monsters!
What did you say?
My sister...
She's been kidnapped by monsters!
What did you say!?
It's all right! I will definitely save her!
It's all right. I'll save her.
Yep, yep. This is it.
A hero has to fight monsters.
Well? Can you feel the intensity?
He wouldn't last long.
Two more pages, huh?
The story's coming along pretty well, isn't it?
It looks like he's headed towards saving the world.
Well, I don't think the world expects anything from this hero.
It's finally my turn, isn't it?
Maybe I'll put a little action in by drawing a battle scene.
Asaba-kun.
There's a first-year looking for you.
H-Hello.
I came to see how your manuscript is coming along.
H-How are you doing?
Do you have any questions?
Well, yeah... I don't know what the hero wants to do any more.
What?
Are those the manuscripts of the other club members?
Yes.
Huh? Am I behind?
No, um...
Sorry.
I know I'm holding you up, but this might end up way
better than anything a Manga Society member could draw.
It's fine!
You've never really felt like a member of the club.
I mean— Not in a bad way.
H-How should I put it... you like manga and anime, but you don't seem like an otaku at all, unlike me.
N-Not to mention how cool you are, so...
Huh?
I, um... S-Sorry.
It's fine.
What?
Nothing. Just got the feeling I got a peek at one of the pages of youth.
The what?
Nevermind, nevermind.
This is the bittersweetness of our...
That's it!
I finished the fourth page!
Oh, really?
I'm late, I'm late!
Oh no,
I overslept!
*jog jog*
What? The hero's wearing a school uniform?
I'm late, I'm late!
Oh no,
I overslept!
*jog jog*
Forget the adventure!
We'll go with a different theme!
What?
Are you stupid?
You can't change the genre now!
Nowadays, having the main character running while eating a piece of toast...
seems plenty adventurous to me.
Everyone, we've forgotten all about an important genre.
That is...
a high-school drama!
Even if we draw a heroic adventure, it'll be nothing more than fantasy!
But the friendship, hard work, and conflict...
experienced in our adolescence are a reality that we can only draw when we, ourselves, are in our adolescence!
Friendship.
Hard work.
Conflict.
Are you stupid?
We're not actually living that life, so it's completely unrelated!
It's okay! Use your imagination!
So, it's imaginary either way.
Out of nowhere, a high school girl...
Well, she's kinda like my ideal heroine.
Jeez, Hero! You're so late!
This hero's hair looks just like someone else's.
Sorry, sorry!
Don't get so mad!
Really?
Don't worry about the details.
What? Already?
Why did they get married so quickly?
Okay, okay. Kanamecchi, you're next.
It's the last page!
You can do it!
Something about your support pisses me off.
Here. I finished the fifth page.
Tsukahara-san, the setting's suddenly changed to M-Mars...
Kaname-kun, you really are the best at everything.
Best at what?! Sorry I suck at drawing.
Come on, Shun, you can do it.
If you don't say something supportive, who will?
Forget about that panel. Keep reading!
It wraps up really nicely!
The celebrated newlyweds create a physical embodiment of their love,
and so the baton of life is passed on—
Just stop looking at that panel!
We've finished all five pages.
It was a lot of work, but I'm glad we did it.
Drawing a manga in the relay format was pretty fun.
Let's switch up the order and do it again some time.
Change the members before you change the order.
U-Um, I'm sorry.
For what?
I just figured we might have made something you're not happy with.
I wouldn't say that.
I could never have drawn five pages by myself.
Thanks for your help.
Yuuki-kun.
Yukki, let's go to the faculty office and make copies for all of us.
What are you doing?
Our first collaboration ended.
Why is the bottom cut off?
A couple of people got really angry.
As though appalled by our foray into the unfamiliar arts,
the high-flying autumn clouds drifted away in boredom.
You And I
There's a hero who I admire.
Most heroes come from a faraway place in the cosmos,
but he...
You want me to draw a manga?
Y-Yes.
A-Anyway, see what you can do.
°
Senpai and I
Manga Society
Did you ask him to do it?
Yes.
Well?
He listened earnestly to what I had to say.
I think he'll do it.
Really?
That's amazing!
This might actually sell.
It might even sell out.
I wonder what he'll draw?
Probably a sports story.
The protagonist will join the Basketball Club,
make friends,
and with a boy like Tsukahara-kun...
I wanna read it now!
If it sells, I guess.
I know, right?
He's not that kind of a hero.
All right! I'm going make a manga for the club about Yuuki-senpai.
I wonder what I should write. A hero is...
The cake is ours!
Stop!
What?
Team Skull, I won't let you do as you please with the Earth!
Transform!
Susume ima!
Go forward now!
Sakebe hora!
Come on, shout!
Ao chikyuu wo mamoru tame,
To defend this blue Earth,
Hero Blue!
Kibou no hikari wo terasu tame,
To shine the light of hope,
Hero Yellow!
Go! Go! Bokura no Homa Ranger!
Go! Go! Our Homa Rangers!
Hero Black!
Hero Pink!
Kyou wo dokoka de Homa Ranger
The Homu Rangers are somewhere out there today
Hero Red!
Together, we are...
Homa Ranger!
High School Fighting Homa Rangers!
So cool.
That's what I'll write.
The five of them pose together, and...
Together, we are...
High School Fighting Homa Rangers!
Why are you the only one wearing your school uniform?
I can't pull off full-body tights.
These aren't full-body tights!
I'm surprised you guys wore them.
Please continue teaching the kids...
in front of the TV the true meaning of bravery.
Don't call it "bravery"!
Th-This is getting really embarrassing!
Stop it!
We're a team. We can't afford to fight now!
You're right.
All right, everyone!
Let's work together to defeat our enemies!
You have to fight, too!
M-Maybe I'll try something else.
What else would suit Yuuki-senpai?
Old man, I'm taking this girl until you pay your debts.
Dad!
Oshun!
Hold it right there.
You're the child-toting samurai!
If you must take someone...
Take him.
He's just been a pain in the neck.
He's too heavy to take anywhere.
I can't come up with anything good.
S-Sorry.
Senpai!
Oh, perfect.
I don't think I'll be done with my manuscript any time soon.
Oh, that's fine.
I'm not close to finishing at all.
Really?
That's no good, Matsushita-kun.
You can do it.
Asaba-senpai is so cool!
Yuuta-senpai's so great,
but Yuuki-senpai has like, a dark side.
His lone wolf attitude is so cool.
That's it!
You again, Asaba?
If you get in trouble again, you'll be expelled!
Please Adopt Me
You're alone, too.
Stop it!
What do you want?
What do you think you're...
I saw a lonely puppy shivering in the rain.
Yes!
This is great.
I'll go with this.
I can't agree to this.
A girl like you isn't suited to be with a brute like Asaba.
Stop it, Tsukahara-kun!
Yuuki's not that kind of person.
Don't say bad things about him!
It seems as if you took care of our Mon recently.
I've come to thank you.
Boss, get him!
Looks like you've got a cutie with you today.
Come here.
Don't touch my girl.
Stop it!
Please! I don't want to see you get hurt any more.
Let go, Matsuoka.
No.
Let go.
No!
Let go!
There's an anime at five I want to watch.
What?
That's weird. Why can't I draw anything?
Could it be...
Hello.
Senpai, what are you doing here?
I pissed off my class's Four-eyes-kun.
I'm hiding from him.
What are you actually doing?
Could it be that Yuuki-senpai isn't heroic at all?
Is that why my stories keep turning out that way?
Watch out!
Thank you, Senpai!
Excuse me. Can we have our ball back, please?
There's a hero I admire.
Most heroes come from a faraway place in the cosmos,
but he's not from a place that far away.
Probably because it'd be too much effort.
But I still think he's greater than any hero.
Let me see your manga when you're done with it, Matsushita-kun.
Yes!
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Giving me the chance to answer you and the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
Budget Review
"Next time: Naked King."