Yuuki. Yuuki, get up already.
I know we're on vacation, but you're sleeping way too much.
Mom says it's nice out, so we should hang our futons outside.
Come on, get—
Ow.
Get up already!
Yuuta, you're so scary.
It's your own fault that you hit your head.
Shut up.
I wanted to keep sleeping.
We've been living together since we were born.
A whole 17 years.
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
Yuuki, you don't have to keep hitting it.
But dusty stuff keeps coming out,
no matter how much I hit it.
Those are the feathers inside.
If you hit it too much, you'll ruin the futon.
Really?
We should get Kaname to do this.
This kinda thing would let him release all his anger.
Where are Mom and Dad?
They went out.
Really? But what about breakfast?
It's already noon.
I'm hungry.
There's leftover curry from yesterday.
Heat it up.
Me?
No, I will.
Hey, at least get dressed before you eat!
You're still wearing your pajamas.
Can't I just wear this?
No.
Yuuta's pretty picky about this kind of stuff.
I'm finished.
Take your dish with you.
Animaga
Musashi-Sakai
Love Stories
Your pajamas.
Huh?
Put them in the washing machine.
And at least try to tidy that bookshelf.
Where are you going?
Out.
If you're going out, pick up some light bulbs.
The bathroom light's out.
Tote Bag
There's a pocket
inside!
An easy-to-use
shape!
Use it for
lunch!!
shopping!!
If I lived on my own, I could take my time picking out books at the bookstore.
If I just sat here and did nothing,
no one would whine about going home now.
Where should I go next?
Homa Rangers Show
Senpai!
Senpai, are you here to see the Homa Rangers show, too?
No, I'm...
Oh, good! I wasn't sure if I'd have the guts to go watch it with all the little kids.
Homa Rangers Show
Hello, everyone!
Hello!
I can't hear you!
You certainly need courage to sit in the front row.
I'm surprised to see you by yourself.
I thought you were always with your friends.
It's nice to go out by myself once in a while.
Huh?
In my case, even when I'm at home,
there's always someone else around.
Oh, no! The evil Skull Squad has appeared!
Looks like they're trying to kidnap good boys and girls!
What? Um...
The Skull Squad has captured a boy from the audience!
But don't fear!
I'm sure the Homa Rangers will come to rescue him!
You'd better call the Homa Rangers!
Huh? S-Save...
Save me, Homa Rangers!
Now, let's all try it together!
Homa Rangers!
What? Senpai?
Light bulbs... Light bulbs...
Really?
You're getting it for us?
Yeah.
Hooray!
Thanks, Dad!
I'm so happy!
Until we got our bunk bed,
we slept side by side in futons on the floor.
So, that huge bed excited us more than any toy ever could.
Should we try climbing up?
Yeah.
Wow, this is amazing.
Yeah, really amazing.
Don't do that, Yuuki.
We're gonna sleep way up here.
I'm gonna sleep on top.
But I want to be on top.
Shoot.
Okay, I'm on top.
You're on the bottom.
Best out of three!
What?
Please! Come on.
Fine.
Shoot.
Shoot!
Okay, now I'm really on top.
Mom, can I put out my futon yet?
Not fair! I wanna be on top!
You can't. You lost at rock, paper, scissors.
Meanie! You're so mean, Yuuta!
Yuuki, I'm turning off the light.
Yuuki.
Hooray! Hooray!
Yuuta, when they bought us that bunk bed, I wonder if—
Yuuki, take the futons to our bedroom.
Oh, right.
He went out.
This must be it.
Yuuta, I bought a light bulb—
I can't breathe, Yuuki-kun.
This must be it.
This must be what they mean by the smell of sunshine.
It's kinda relaxing.
What is it, Yuuki?
What's wrong?
I'm gonna sleep here.
What?
Good night.
Just for tonight.
It's cramped.
Yuuki, promise me that you'll sleep in the bottom bunk tomorrow.
Yuuta, your hair still smells like shampoo.
Are you listening?
We're not little kids anymore.
You have to learn how to sleep by yourself.
That's not it.
I just wanted to sleep on top, too.
You And Me.
The year is finally coming to a close.
I'm sure a lot of families out there
are busy cleaning their homes.
Darling, if you have time to watch TV,
I'm also really busy at this time of year,
why don't you go change the light bulb in the bedroom?
so I'd appreciate any sort of help.
Okay, okay.
Yuuta-kun, Yuuki-kun, do you have enough rags?
Yeah.
Where's the new detergent?
Oh, right. We have to go buy some.
This has been here for years.
Didn't you draw this...
Hey Yuuki, help me out here.
We won't get it done, otherwise.
I'm doing it.
I'm deciding what to keep and what to throw out.
You've been saying that, but you haven't made any progress.
Animaga
We've been together since we were born,
and we do the same thing every New Year's Eve.
Come on. Grab a rag.
Yuuki.
Oh, Yuuta.
Are we gonna have New Year's soba—
Musashi-Sakai
Love Stories
Yuuta, you're dripping all over!
The water! My manga!
Huh? Oh, sorry.
What are you doing?
It'll be fine. It's not that much.
This is terrible.
You'd better pay me for this stuff.
You'd better pay me back for this, Yuuta.
Pay you?
Then you should've done the cleaning yourself.
I told you to do it, but you refused.
You're gonna get mad at me instead of apologizing?
I apologized for the manga.
No, you didn't.
You don't think you did anything wrong.
You always ignore me when I tell you to do things.
That's because you always go on and on about every little thing.
Then do it before I have to tell you to.
Yuuta-kun, Yuuki-kun, can one of you clean the tub?
Say, the tub...
Yuuta-kun, where's Yuuki-kun going?
I don't know.
It's your fault.
I haven't even told you what happened.
I don't have to hear it to know.
I'm sure you made Yuuta mad because you wouldn't help him clean, right?
No, it's Yuuta's fault.
He didn't wring out his rag enough.
Are you saying you actually helped?
I really did.
I was deciding which Animaga issues to keep.
I knew you weren't helping him clean.
You don't usually fight, but I'm not surprised that you argued over something so stupid.
Go home. I'm not getting involved.
No. I'll live here from now on.
What are you, a little kid?
Oh? I don't mind you living here with us.
Really, Mom?
Of course not!
And don't call her Mom!
But Kaname-kun, you're so cold!
I hope someone takes me away from you,
so you can finally realize how important I am.
Don't give me that.
You're the one who needs to realize how ridiculous it is to use your son's friends to make him feel bad.
I'm a lot nicer than Kaname, ma'am.
Don't make it sound like you're having an affair with my mom!
Go home already!
Don't wanna!
You're just making this harder on yourself!
Seriously, go home!
Don't wanna!
Wait a minute. Don't call him.
I mean it. Don't.
Hello, Yuuta? It's me.
Your idiot brother just showed up at my house.
Can you take him home?
He's getting in our way.
What? You, too?
It's not like I don't understand,
but don't stick me in the middle—
Hey, wait! Hey!
What did Yuuta say?
He said you don't have to come home.
What are you going to do?
Yuuta's really mad.
Come on. Just go home and apologize.
Okay, fine.
I'll go get a change of clothes.
Apologize, I said!
Yuuta-kun, can you take out the garbage?
Sure.
He thinks that no matter what he does, I'll always forgive him.
It's always been that way. I always...
That's right. We...
How long are you going to stay here?
Go home already!
No.
Please don't ask why. Just let me stay here.
I already heard about your stupid fight!
I won't ask you about...
your relationship with your mother, either.
Why not?! Just ask!
There's nothing to tell—we just a have a normal mother-son relationship!
If you wait, you'll only make it harder to apologize.
Is that the neighborhood circular?
As a new member of the Tsukahara household,
I should go introduce myself.
Hey!
Yuuta.
What are you doing?
Everyone's busy on New Year's Eve.
If you stay too late, you'll just get in their way.
Let's go.
Your coat.
Yuuki-kun, you're going home?
After everything you said,
Sorry for bothering you.
you still came to get him.
That's why Yuuki is so—
Just for today.
Huh?
I'm going easy on him, just for today.
Yuuta, what's wrong?
That's Dad's plate.
What am I going to do?
Yuuki?
Are you sure about this?
I'm sure. It'll be fine.
It'll be our secret.
That should do it.
Now that I've protected you, I'm an accomplice to the crime.
Even if we're found out, we'll both get in trouble.
So it'll be okay.
It'll be okay.
Um, Yu—
Ow.
You headbutted me.
I see. Are you really that mad, Yuuki-kun?
No, I just slipped.
It's fine.
I'm sure you're really mad at me, aren't you?
I'm not mad. Honestly, I just slipped.
There's ice over here.
I slipped on this and...
Look, Yuuta. Look at it!
Yuuta.
We're sorry.
Huh? Did we have a plate like this?
I don't know what happened, but it's not a big deal.
There's only a few minutes left of this year.
A lot of things have happened this year.
I wonder what next year will hold.
Yuuta-kun, Yuuki-kun, there's more soba if you want it.
I'm praying for a good year for you all.
Honey, come quick.
There's no Shichimi spice left.
Now, it's time for the countdown. Is everyone ready?
What? Isn't there some more in the refrigerator?
Five, four, three, two, one...
That's odd. Did I put it in the cupboard?
Shichimi
There isn't any.
Happy New Year!
That's weird. I thought I put it in there.
Well, that's that.
Have a happy new year.
It's not there. We never put it there.
Don't we?
You, too.
Where could it have gone?
I just bought it today.
In The Steam
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "The Hem of that Sky"
The Hem of the Sky