I kissed Mamiya.
I was nervous.
Ah, she's so cute!
Fuyuki.
What?
Dinner's ready.
I'll be right down!
Shun-nii, I love you!
What?
Um, okay...
We're having tonkatsu tonight.
I love tonkatsu too!
Since I'm only slightly older than my brother,
I'm constantly worried, maybe a little too much,
that he'll lose, break,
or hurt the things he loves.
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
Here.
Thanks.
The weather is perfect for a Sunday.
What kind of weather is that?
Ouch. Hot...
Why are you cooling your fingers on my earlobe?
Because it's close.
Really?
I didn't realize it was closer than your own earlobe.
What?
Yuuta, your earlobes are soft.
Most people's earlobes are soft.
They say that people with soft earlobes are perverts.
Really?
Yeah. Which means that most people are perverts.
What are we going to do if Shun's earlobes are soft?
Incoming call...
Matsuoka Shun
Speak of the devil.
Hello?
Yuuta-kun, what am I going to do?
Shun?
What... What should I do?
Fuyuki... Fuyuki...
What's going on?
I'm not sure, but apparently
something really bad has happened to Shun's brother.
What does that have to do with me?
Are you okay, Shun-chan?!
Was it Fuyuki?
Did that pervert bully you?
That bastard!
You stay here!
I'll go beat him up for you!
Hold your horses. That's not it.
What is it, then?
Fuyuki...
kissed Mamiya-san.
What? That's all?
"That's all"? Don't you think they're moving too fast?
They're only second years!
That's not really fast, though.
As his older brother, I don't know what I should say to him.
Hey... Can I go home now?
Hey Shun-nii, have you seen my phone?
I see you're all not doing anything on your day off, as usual.
Shut it.
You're the one who created this situation
by kissing your little girlfriend.
Huh? Oh.
So what?
One little k-kiss is nothing to get so worked up about.
Where's my phone?
Where'd it go?
Shun-nii asked me about it, so I just had to tell him.
Well, of course we kissed.
We're dating, after all.
Whoops! This is the remote.
Hey, it was only a kiss.
Just look at him. You have to let it go.
Just a kiss?
Jeez, lovers could do much worse than just kissing.
Kyoko, I love you.
I won't let you leave tonight.
Satoru.
No, Satoru. The stars are watching.
I don't care.
Hey, you perv!
What? Don't you ever shut up?
Don't give me that.
You've become a fully-fledged pervert over one little kiss.
Middle schoolers shouldn't go any further than that!
What? Is there a law against it?
You idiot!
Even if the law allows it, my pride never will!
Right, right. It must be tough, having no luck with the ladies even though you're in high school.
You bastard! Don't think that you've won just because you have a girlfriend!
Now, now.
You lost the moment you picked a serious fight with a middle schooler.
Hey, Big Brother Shun!
Listen to what your little brother's saying!
What are you thinking?
Middle schoolers should study together, support each other,
and build friendships!
Listen to what Mother Shun's saying.
Shun-chan.
In any case, as long as you're a student,
you're still far too young!
I don't know about that.
What?
Between a third and half of all people have had their first experience by high school.
Huh? What? Wh-Where does it say that?
Where? Where?
I Asked Everyone
Questionnaire
Seriously? That's kinda depressing.
Shun, did you buy this?
No, my sister did.
But half is amazingly high.
That's one in every two people.
Kanamecchi?!
I knew it.
Valedictorians aren't prestigious. They're perverts.
Why me?
Just how closely do you try to look with those glasses?
Does he do it with them on?
Are you all braindead?!
Half of all people have their first kiss by high school.
Look, "first experience" doesn't mean your first kiss. It means s—
Where are you going, Fuyuki?
Damn it. I thought that was my chance to escape.
I'm not done talking to you.
Haven't you said enough already?
I have a date with Mamiya today.
What?!
Hey, I'm sure you know, but you can't try anything!
Make sure you stay out of your g-girlfriend's room, and don't go to h-hotels or places like that.
I know.
Matsuoka.
Mamiya.
Sorry I'm late.
It's fine. I just got here, too.
Let's go.
Okay.
"I just got here, too."
That's the first time I've actually heard anyone say that.
It's the first time I've heard it in real life, too.
Who are you trying to impress?
He's not trying to impress anyone.
We came here to watch him.
Who wouldn't?
We have to make sure thatpervert in the explosion of puberty doesn't cross the line.
If adults like us don't do it, who will?
No one needs to do it.
They seem to be having fun.
Yes, well...
I find this sort of thing very interesting.
I'm here because I'm genuinely worried about Fuyuki and Mamiya-san.
But the rest of you...
The rest of you are all thinking dirty thoughts!
Sheesh!
Sorry.
Hey, what does that mean?
Shut up and watch.
Go now!
Go now, shout it out,
Location: Saitama
Shout it out!
To protect our blue earth.
To shine the light of hope.
Go, go, everyone's a Homa Ranger
Someone out there is a Homa Ranger
Location: Saitama
Go! Go!
Everyone's a Homa Ranger.
Today, someone out there is a Homa Ranger.
All together!
Homa Ranger, yeah!
Homa Ranger
Homa Rangers are the best!
points
What?! 61?!
See?
It's your fault for trying a song that you only know the chorus to.
It's my fault?
That's right.
You lost a whole load of points because of that hairdo.
My hair's got nothing to do with it!
points
Shun, do you want to sing something with me?
Oh, no. I'm not very good at singing.
Sing something.
Otherwise, Chizuru will take the stage again.
What do you want to do?
In that case...
hana ga hirahira odotte minna egao ni naretara
When the flowers are dancing and everyone's smiling,
sore de it's all right boku datte minna to ureshiku naru
then it's all right, and even I'll be happy with everyone
Shun-chan's amazing.
Yeah, he's so off that he's almost harmonizing.
That doesn't make any sense.
Next! Kanamecchi, you sing something.
What? No thanks.
We'll pull up something you can sing.
Come on. Take the mic.
He looks like he's running for office.
Huh? Kaname, did you declare your candidacy?
What?
warukunai, warukunai
Not my fault, not my fault
ore no sei janai
It's not my fault
makikomareteru dake omaera ni
You guys just dragged me into it
kyoumi nai kyoumi nai
I'm not interested, not interested
dakara hottoke yo
So leave me alone
ita soba kara sonna ni ore wo komarasetai no ka
You're still here? Do you want to bother me that badly?
iwayuru yuutousei datte sono bun douryoku wa
Even so-called honor students have to do their share...
I don't know the rest, so whoever wants to sing can finish.
Kaname-kun, that was amazing!
Come on. He sang it normally.
Without showing the real intent
Softly hidden behind glasses
You're supposed to sound ridiculous or something.
Well, I suppose there's nothing more ridiculous than Tsukahara Kaname actually being a decent singer.
Ah, I try to loosen my necktie
sometimes
Shut up already.
Anyway, we've just been doing karaoke for a while now.
Don't you care about Fuyuki anymore?
They haven't really done anything yet,
and it seems like they're just singing over in the next room.
I think I might have been worrying over nothing.
We shouldn't have followed them on their date.
Don't sweat it, Shun-chan.
They don't know we followed them.
Okay, let's sing a ton more today!
Yeah!
You And Me.
I hear the song of the frog...
The room next door sounds lively.
I wonder if it's a group of little kids.
Yeah, I get the feeling it's a group of guys
who have the same mental age as kids.
Let's sing some more, too.
Isn't this one on TV all the time?
Oh, right.
Here, happy birthday.
Huh? How did you...
Did I tell you when my birthday was?
I asked your friends.
Really?
Can I open it?
Yeah.
It's so cute!
Thanks, Matsuoka.
Oh, wait.
What about you, Matsuoka?
When's your birthday?
Mine's December 30th.
I see.
So it's already passed.
I'll still get you a present, anyway.
You don't need to do that.
That's not why I gave you one.
I want to give you something.
Tell me. What do you want?
Matsuoka?
Um, well...
Can I touch your chest?
What?
M-Mine?
B-But my chest is... um, small...
It's not that I want to fondle big ones or anything...
G-Go ahead.
What? Really?
Yeah. As long as it's over my clothes.
Okay. Then...
Here goes!
They're soft.
Your earlobes.
What?
Shun, yours are soft, too.
Is it bad to have soft earlobes?
I wouldn't quite go that far.
Right, Yuuta-kun?
Yuuta?
What's wrong, Yuutan?
It's too early for a break.
I just...
I just thought that it wouldn't be impossible to do it in a karaoke booth.
Huh? Not impossible to do what?
Oh, that again?
Karaoke
Half Price
for Students
I guess it's not impossible...
Yeah, even a karaoke booth could work.
Hey, guys!
You're always trying to pin something on him.
They're not doing anything. I'm sure they're behaving fine—
You're right.
A karaoke booth's a triple threat: It's locked,
soundproofed, and has soft couches.
I didn't even think about that.
How long did they say they were using the room for?
Didn't they ask for an hour to start?
What? Is an hour a long time? Or is it sh-short?
I don't know.
It wouldn't be impossible.
It's possible to request an extension in some cases, too.
I haven't heard any singing coming from that room for a while!
Fuyuki!
Calm down, Shun-chan!
Why are you always doing things that make me sad?
I-It'll be okay! I'm telling you!
Where did you pull that yell from?
Wh-What am I going to do?
I didn't think about what would happen after I touched them.
S-Sorry.
I'm sorry, Mamiya. Sorry!
Sorry!
I didn't mean to cry.
I turned this into a bad experience for Matsuoka,
since he had to apologize so much.
Sorry I took so long, Matsuoka—
Huh? I'm sorry, I'm in the wrong room.
Mamiya-san.
Matsuoka's brother.
It's nice to see you again.
I see you've come here to have some fun, too.
Oh.
U-Um...
Mamiya-san, have you been crying?
What?
Um, Mamiya, I'm sorry about what...
Fuyuki...
Shun-nii?
You idiot!
That was close!
What was that for?
You made Mamiya-san cry!
Shut up.
I wasn't trying to make her cry.
And this doesn't have anything to do with you!
It does!
Why?
I'm your brother!
Sh-Shun-chan, you should get the full story from—
I don't care what happened.
Why would you make the girl you love cry?
Why can't you take care of her properly?
You were acting so happy every day just because you'd kissed Mamiya-san!
Um, sir?
Oh, it's nothing. Nothing.
Right, guys? We're just friends singing some karaoke...
But you...
But Fuyuki, you're always looking at dirty magazines and videos!
Whenever you get into trouble, you hide them under my bed!
We get it!
We get it, Shun-chan!
Okay? Come on.
My brother always accepts that I worry too much.
It's as inevitable as the breath of spring melting the cold of winter.
It's cold, isn't it?
You're so lucky, Matsuoka.
Your scarf looks warm.
Hey...
Sorry about today.
I'm sorry for what I did.
But I really didn't mean to upset you.
I just... well...
Your earlobes are soft.
Pervert.
I'll walk you home.
Okay.
I had fun today.
Why did you just let go of my hand?
Huh? Oh, no reason.
Jeez! You don't even know what should embarrass you and what shouldn't.
I-I didn't say I was embarrassed!
Then why did you let go?
Yuutan, Shun-chan. Let's go home.
How has the pervert been doing?
Are Fuyuki and Mamiya-san getting along?
Yes, thanks for asking.
They studied together today.
It looks like they're going to work on their friendship first.
As his brother, I'm relieved.
Oh, really?
As a fellow man, I'm starting to worry about you, Shun.
Studying, huh?
I wonder what they're studying.
I don't think Fuyuki will learn his lesson that easily.
That's not true.
They said they were studying together today, too.
Mamiya-san's parents aren't home today, so they can study
in her room without any interruptions.
In Mamiya-san's room?
Yes.
In Mamiya-san's room, which has a bed?
Just the two of them?
Fuyuki!
This looks like trouble.
Could it be? Could it really, really be this time?
You call it "trouble," but you're smiling.
We can't help it. We're boys.
Us Boys
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "Mix Juice."