Our seventeenth winter has arrived.
It's not as if anything has changed, though.
Mandarins
Who here peels the white bits off of tangerines before eating them?
Who doesn't?
Well, if you think about it,
there's no reason to remove them.
I heard that the white bits are good for you.
It was on TV yesterday.
Mandarins
Seriously?!
There's even less reason to peel them off now.
I wonder what's in it that's good for you.
I don't know.
Probably some vitamin or something.
Whatever, just eat them.
But if you eat too many, don't your hands turn yellow?
They do.
Is that bad for you?
But the herbal medicine, Chenpi,
is made from tangerine skins, isn't it?
Chenpi?
What?
Mandarins
Nothing.
I was just wondering where exactly
this pointless conversation was going.
You guys must have nothing to do.
Wow, talk about rude!
You know, we're always very busy, thinking up ways
to spend our free time!
In other words, you've got nothing to do.
Today's tangerines aren't very sweet.
Mandarins
Well, if you squeeze them, it makes them sweeter.
This guy's telling us to squeeze them...
What a pervert.
How do you get that?!
Such a dirty mind, Kanamecchi.
Look who's talking!
Instead of staying in the nice, warm classroom this winter,
Mandarins
we're out here together, for no particular reason.
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
I'm really freezing.
It's because we were eating tangerines out there.
Should we eat them in the classroom tomorrow?
You're bringing tangerines again tomorrow?
Sorry, but my relatives sent us a ton.
My family can't eat all of them ourselves.
Who cares?
Winter is tangerine season.
Tangerines are good, but I want some oden, too.
Or udon.
That sounds good.
Yeah, I'd sure like to warm up with some hot food in me.
Leave the warmth to me!
Is this what you meant by "warmth"?
Yup. He's nice and warm, isn't he?
Well, I am warming up.
Does that feel nice, Master?
Who are you calling "Master"?
Huh?
I feel like I've seen something similar to this shape before...
It looks like you two! It looks just like you!
Doesn't it?
This cat certainly is cute like Yuuta-kun and Yuuki-kun.
Not that.
Look at their eyes! Their eyes!
Then look at the pattern on the cat's back.
Besides, in what way are Yuutan and Yukki cute and cat-like?
In kindergarten...
They were just like kittens. Weren't they just the cutest?
You're asking me if they were cute?
I didn't know Yukki and Yuutan in kindergarten.
Oh, right.
Let's get a picture.
Yukki, Yuutan, stand next to the master.
Come on, hurry up.
Kaname-kun, does your mother like tangerines?
I don't think she dislikes them.
Then can we go deliver some to her after this?
She's always taking care of us.
Why are you guys here, too?
And why are you eating?
Seconds!
Coming right up.
Me, too.
And me, please.
Just a second.
How much are you going to eat?
Show a little restraint when you're a guest.
Sorry that we're staying for dinner...
It's fine.
Having someone to cook for makes it worth cooking.
But, this is seriously good!
I'm sure you'll make a wonderful wife one day.
She's already a wife. Dad's.
It really is delicious.
I'm so happy to hear that.
Kaname-kun never compliments me,
no matter what I cook for him.
Kanamecchi, you're so cold.
Kaname, that's the sort of thing that leads to divorce.
How could it? She's my mom!
I'm stuffed.
I don't feel like going home anymore.
Kanamecchi, I'm staying here tonight.
What are you babbling about?
Go home.
It's fine.
You don't have school tomorrow.
It's not fine.
Yeah! Why can't I stay over?!
Because I'll have to look after this obnoxious monkey all night all by myself—
Then we'll stay, too.
That'll be even more annoying!
Kanamecchi, come on!
No way.
Besides, you guys don't have a change of clothes.
Oh, I'll go home and get some, then.
Ow!
If you're going home, just stay there!
All right. We're sleeping over at Kanamecchi's tonight!
Hey, don't just go off and decide—
I need to get my toothbrush.
Let me use your shampoo.
Hey!
Thank you for letting us stay.
Don't mention it.
Okay, Kaname, bye bye for now.
None of you come back!
The bath's ready for you. You can take turns going in.
Okay!
Okay, I'll go in first.
What gives you the right to go first?
You've got a point.
Kaname-kun, you go first.
What? Let's decide it with rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
Shun-chan's such a good kid.
Unlike you, who tried to jump in first.
Hey, guys, does Shun-chan...
Why are you whispering?
Just talk normally. It's not like he's in the room.
Oh, right.
Does Shun-chan ever get mad?
Of course he does.
I think Shun's actually pretty manly.
He's like, very headstrong, and...
Come on, Yuutan. Don't get so serious.
This is about kinda wanting to see such a cute,
good-humored kid like him get a little mad, right?
That's not what we're talking about, either.
Chizuru, you did think that Shun was a girl when you first met him.
Well, he does get angry,
but in a cute way, with his cheeks all puffed up.
That doesn't count as "angry."
Right, Mr. Expert?
Why am I an expert about this?
Because no one's better at getting angry than you, of course.
Whose fault is that?!
Don't fight, you two.
W-Wait a minute, Yuutan. Was that...
I'm Shun.
If Shun was here, he'd try to mediate,
so I decided to try it.
That doesn't sound anything like him!
Shun-chan's more like this:
Come on, guys. Don't fight...
That's not it either, Chizuru.
Why can't we all just get along?
What? Yuuki-kun, that's not right, either.
You guys look like idiots from over here.
Jeez, Kaname-kun, why don't you try going along with us sometimes?
I wanna see Kaname-kun's Shun.
Stop it! It's weird.
We're serious. You should try it, Kaname-kun.
Not a chance.
Then, why don't we talk about when we were in kindergarten?
We can talk about Kaori-sensei, or Kaori-sensei,
or maybe even Kaori-sensei.
Oh, I want to hear all about it!
You dirty cheats!
That's how badly we want to see you do it.
If you understand, just do it already.
Oh, I understand.
I understand just how annoying you all are.
Do it, do it!
You better not tell anyone else.
I'm only gonna do it once.
Okay.
Why do you guys always have to fight?
Can't you try to get along?
Welcome back, Shun.
Shun!
Wait! This isn't what it looks like!
Kaname-kun, I didn't know you talked like that sometimes.
Huh?
I'm not saying it's bad or weird...
I think it's good for people to have different sides to them.
What? But, I was...
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
I won.
See you guys later.
Hold on a sec, Yuutan.
Yukki, you go with him.
What? Why?
Yeah, do it.
Help us save some time!
If we don't get a move on, we'll end up getting to bed late.
That's no reason for us to go in together.
You're twins, aren't you?
One and the same, right?
It'll be a two-for-one deal.
What are you saying, valedictorian?
That's not what it means.
It's only at times like this when you realize that we're twins.
Quit complaining and get going already.
I didn't think they'd actually do it.
You're such a child.
Huh? That was fast.
We couldn't relax in there together.
Really?
Kaname-kun, Chizuru-kun, it's one of you two next.
Right, come on.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
Oh, come on!
After all of that, I'm last?!
That's karma for your actions today, monkey.
Hey.
Keep an eye on these perverts.
What were you guys doing?
We were just doing a touch of peeping.
Quit acting like idiots.
Do it again and I'll beat you.
I couldn't relax at all.
Go on then, monkey.
No.
If I go, I'm sure you guys will talk about me
behind my back or imitate me.
I don't want that!
It'll be fine, Chizuru-kun.
Yeah, don't worry.
We don't want to talk about you, anyway.
I don't want that, either!
So, which is it?
Quit complaining and get going!
You And Me.
That monkey ruined my quiet night indoors.
But isn't it more fun when it's lively?
I feel like Chizuru-kun's been with us forever, somehow.
I always end up talking about the past because of it.
I wonder if that bothers him...
What? I'm sure it's fine.
Phew, that was great.
Kanamecchi, your bath is great.
It's so big and clean.
Who are you?
Oh, the futons are all ready!
It's a miracle you can fit four futons in a normal room, don't you think?
Your room's pretty big, if nothing else.
No, the miracle is what's going
on with your hair right now.
You guys sleep wherever.
Don't let him sleep!
Don't think I'm going to let you slink off to sleep!
We're gonna have lots more fun tonight!
Wake up!
W-Wait... You guys!
It's true, though.
There's nothing to play with in Kaname's room.
I know.
This room's only good for studying and sleeping.
I can't sleep with you on my bed! Get off!
Stay up, then.
It's always you, isn't it? You little...
Kaname-kun, what about that?
Don't you have it any more?
Wow, a telescope!
Kanamecchi, I didn't know you had something like this.
I forgot I had it.
We all did some stargazing back in elementary school.
We stayed over at Kaname-kun's house and...
Wasn't it our summer research project?
Hey, do you think if we look at the moon, we'll see a "Cramer"?
Any "Cramer" would live on Earth, so no.
You can see craters, though.
There's a full moon tonight,
so I'm sure you'll be able to see them.
Maybe.
I don't think so.
Even if it's a full moon, if Kaname's hogging the telescope,
we won't get to see a single star, let alone any craters.
You're right.
Why don't you guys try becoming stars instead?
I'll even help you out.
The North Star.
Is that really it?
Dunno. Just guessing.
What?
Is it me? Am I the North Star?
Does the world revolve around me?
Constellation
Picture Book
You might be right.
You always confuse people into circling crazily around you.
What is that supposed to mean?
I wonder what constellations we can see right now.
Orion?
Isn't that it?
Look, you can even see Canis Major and Canis Minor.
Canis Major
Sirius
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
If you connect these three constellations,
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Rigel
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Rigel
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Rigel
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Rigel
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Rigel
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Winter Triangle
Rigel
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Winter Triangle
Sirius
Orion
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Sirius
Orion
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Sirius
Orion
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Sirius
Orion
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Sirius
Orion
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Sirius
Orion
you get the Winter Triangle.
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Sirius
Orion
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Sirius
Orion
Winter Triangle
Procyon
Canis Minor
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Sirius
Orion
Winter Triangle
Betelgeuse
Rigel
Sirius
Orion
Winter Triangle
Yuuta-kun and Yuuki-kun's constellation should be nearby.
Look.
Castor
Pollux
Gemini
You're right.
I heard that there's a myth behind Gemini.
The older brother, Castor, was a master horseman.
The younger brother, Pollux, was a master boxer.
The two brothers got along very well together.
But one day, Castor got involved
in a petty quarrel and was killed.
The grieving Pollux tried to kill himself,
but because he was immortal, he couldn't.
He asked his father, Zeus, to help him,
and Zeus turned them both into a constellation
so that they could always be together.
Yukki, I know you love your brother,
but don't do it!
Hey, that's the story of Castor-kun and Pollux-kun.
You have to overcome your grief
and live for your brother's sake too!
I'm not too bothered by it,
but could you stop acting like I'm dead?
This myth is just too sad.
The story behind Ursa Major
is a tragedy of love and hate, too.
A nymph fell in love with Zeus and bore his child,
but his angry wife turned the nymph and her son into bears.
Ursa Major
Ursa Minor
Big Dipper
Pole star
The dramas of the night sky are so messed up.
People of the past had such difficult love lives.
I'm sure there's people like that today, too.
Like people in love with kindergarten
teachers much older than them.
Oh, you mean Kaori-sensei? Just kidding.
How long ago was that?
I bet Kanamecchi's still into older women.
She just happens to be older, too!
He's mad now!
It must be true.
You're such a pervert, Kaname-kun.
"Too"?
No, I just...
What are you doing down there, Mom?
Oh, nothing.
You liar. You've been eavesdropping on us, haven't you?
N-No, I wasn't.
You're all still awake, so I came to ask you
if you wanted anything to eat.
I didn't come to ask you how much of an age gap
counts as acceptable for you.
So you were eavesdropping!
I'm so sorry. Did we wake you?
It's fine.
Don't mind me.
Just carry on talking about that last topic.
In great detail.
Like hell we will!
Come on, Mom. Go back to your room and sleep.
But it's just getting to the good part!
I might have a chance!
Just go to bed.
I can't see anything.
Let me look.
We should go to sleep.
What?
Is it that late already?
Looks like it.
It's cold in here. Close the window.
And the curtains.
Leave them open.
Let's look at the stars while we sleep.
I can't sleep if it's too dark.
Fine.
I'm turning off the light.
Okay. Good night.
Good night.
Hey...
Shut up, you guys!
I'm trying to sleep!
How long are you gonna keep jabbering on?
It's not us.
Chizuru's talking and laughing by himself.
But Yukki just said you should
sit cross-legged when you look at the Northern Cross!
What's so funny about that?
Come on.
We're really going to sleep this time.
Hey...
You little...
I know. This'll be the last time.
Shun-chan, what was everyone like
in elementary school?
What were we like?
No one's really changed.
Kaname was class president,
and Shun was... already Shun.
Huh? What does that mean?
Who was the most popular with the ladies?
Wasn't it Yuuta?
Yeah, he was.
What? Let's not talk about this.
Is it time for a confession, Yuuta-sama?
Yuuta-kun's always been nice.
And he could run really fast, too.
He was fast?
Fast kids get all the girls in elementary school.
What about Yukki, then?
He runs fast, too.
It's not like Yuuki didn't have girls chasing him,
but he's never been all that sociable,
and he absolutely hates groups.
What a waste.
He's so lucky.
Yuutan's always been popular,
and he was the first one of us to get a girlfriend.
Hey, Yuutan, when you were dating Takahashi-san,
did you guys kiss?
No.
Do we really have to talk about this now?
Come on. You can tell us the truth today.
Did you?
I just told you. No.
And stop trying to listen in, over there.
It wouldn't surprise me if you didn't.
You weren't going out for very long.
You guys did break up rather quickly.
Things seemed to be going well, too.
You went to the bookstore together and stuff.
I go to the bookstore with Yuuta all the time.
There's no need to get so jealous.
Even though he complains,
Yuuta always waits for me to finish shopping.
He always wakes me up, too.
And he's always been nice to Shun, not just me.
He's the first to notice when someone's in trouble,
and he helps them out.
Yuuta's always looking out for everyone else.
That's because you demand his attention every day.
I don't know anything about that.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Stop saying that.
Do you guys remember the time
we got first place in the school choir contest,
and Watanabe-sensei...
Yeah, he cried his eyes out.
Yeah, I know.
Kaname, you teared up, too.
No, I—
Those tears were more beautiful than the medal we won.
Shut up.
Do you remember the song we sang?
Oh, I guess you don't know who Watanabe-sensei is.
Huh? It's fine.
It's interesting.
We haven't really talked about
this sort of thing before.
You're right.
What? Who was that?
Sorry.
Shun, you should've asked for more at dinner.
You guys asked for too much.
I'm kinda hungry, too.
Right! Let's go the convenience store.
Now?
Let's go.
Even during cold winters,
I'm sure the rabbit in the moon keeps on hopping...
In a moon that quietly illuminates even the darkest of nights...
I'm hungry. I'm gonna eat so much.
Me, too.
I'm gonna eat a ton.
I want oden. Or udon.
Hot food would be great right now.
Do you guys want to eat those tangerines Shun-chan brought?
You really shouldn't. It's late.
It'll be fine.
We're gonna stay up all night.
The Rabbit in the Moon Hops All Night Long
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "Mary's Christmas."