Oh, a cat!
A cat?
Where?
There. Look!
Doesn't that cloud look like a cat?
Yeah.
You could call it a cat... or maybe a dog or a raccoon.
What a convenient silhouette.
Well, that cloud over there definitely looks like a cat!
See? It's running with a fish in its mouth.
It's all messed up.
I bet the master artist, Tsukahara, drew that cat.
The reason why the sky's so blue is because it's depressed by Kaname's drawing skills.
Shut up.
Class is starting.
Let's hurry up!
Wait!
Spring.
Pink cherry blossom petals dance like butterflies,
and white clouds drift lazily across the sky.
We're now third years at Homare High School.
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
Even though we're third years, absolutely nothing's changed.
We changed classrooms, didn't we?
For some reason, changing classrooms makes me feel like we've become third years.
Kaname-kun and Yuuta-kun are in Class 4...
and we're in Class 3.
Yuuki-kun and Chizuru-kun,
I look forward to spending the year with you.
Don't bother. You won't make it.
You're gonna miss, Chizuru.
You'll miss, walk over to pick it up, and then drop it in the trashcan like you always do.
You don't even have a comeback.
I'm concentrating!
Shut up for a second!
Yuuki-kun, that was amazing.
Hey, why'd you have to get it in before me?
This sucks!
Did you really have to put that kinda pressure on me?
No, I just threw it away.
I wanted to throw it away, and it just happened to go in when I threw it.
You're putting tons of pressure on him.
Damn it!
Then... Then if I make this, I'll run into Mary today at...
school!
Sh-Shun-chan!
Huh?
Oh, um... It's nothing.
Masaki-chan.
Construction paper?
Are you going to use that to make something?
Oh, yeah.
I have to write the brackets for the sports festival tournament.
Oh, right. The sports festival's coming up.
I'm part of the Athletics Committee.
The Athletics Committee?
I lost at rock, paper, scissors.
I see.
Um...
Shun-chan, what event will you be participating in at the sports festival?
Me?
I'm playing volleyball.
Me, too! Me, too!
We're all playing volleyball.
I'm actually pretty good at volleyball.
I don't think it really fits my image, though.
No, it totally fits you.
I'll d-definitely come to cheer you on.
Really?
I'll have to do my best, then.
Yeah.
Oh, right.
I need to go borrow some markers.
You need to carry even more stuff?
You should've asked someone in your class to help you.
Can you handle it by yourself?
No, asking for help too rashly could be even more dangerous.
She might end up getting carried herself.
I'm not that small!
See you later.
Ouch.
With arms that strong, she can definitely manage it without anyone's help.
And every time, you manage to make Masaki angry without anyone's help either.
What'd you say?!
I'm always genuinely worried about Mary, you—
Hey, does she have any friends in her class?
Well, you know...
I've just never seen her with anyone.
Well, I guess she is always by herself.
That isn't good.
School's a place to learn how to interact with others.
You're one to talk.
She probably just doesn't care too much
about whether she has friends or not.
Maybe, but...
I hope Masaki makes friends in her new class.
Satou-san!
You got the construction paper and markers?
I'm sorry.
I'm on the Athletics Committee, too, so I should've...
Maybe I'll play dodgeball.
But there's only one space left.
We won't be able to play together.
Then maybe basketball.
I'm getting everyone to decide what events they want to participate in at the sports festival.
If we do basketball, then we can't...
Oh, how about volleyball?
What do you want to do, Satou-san?
What's left?
Basketball and soft tennis.
Also, dodgeball has one more spot open.
I'll play dodgeball, then.
What? Really?
Yeah. That's not okay?
It's fine, but...
Soft tennis would be okay, too.
Then you should pick that, Yuko.
I don't want to do it by myself.
I don't want to!
Anyway...
We're supposed to get people to referee when they have free time during the day of the festival.
So I thought we could talk with everyone about who'll referee—
Huh? Wh-What?
I-I want to fill in that one.
Huh? Here?
Shun-chan's class.
Carefully, carefully...
Satou-san's always with Yuuki-senpai and his friends,
so I figured she had lots of friends, but...
Please let Shun-chan's class win.
Let them win. Let them win!
See you later.
Bye bye.
Why is our class the only one like this?
Who knows?
Because we have flowers blooming in our heads?
I've got it! It means we're VIPs!
It's like we're the favorites to win!
I see.
You're not a team. You're a trio of idiots.
Kaname-kun, Yuuta-kun.
Are you here to cheer for your class?
No, we're here to play.
We're up against you next.
You're kidding! Seriously?
Oh boy! This'll be an easy win for us, then?
I don't think we're gonna lose to a nerd who doesn't carry anything heavier than his study guides!
Look who's talking.
I don't think someone as short as you will be blocking any of our spikes.
What'd you say?!
Height doesn't decide a match!
You have to use this when you play sports. This, right here.
Then you've already lost.
Peach
Yogurt
Let the game between Class 3-3 and Class 3-4 begin!
Go get 'em, Shun-chan!
Okay.
Crap!
Kaname.
No, you don't! Chizuru block!
Yeah, Tsukahara!
Yeah!
Stop that.
Don't worry, Chizuru-kun.
We're just getting started.
That's right.
You're just starting to grow, Chizuru.
Shut up!
And you should chase after the ball like your life depends on it!
I'm doing that.
You haven't moved!
But I'm gritting my teeth really hard.
You're just suppressing a yawn!
Not bad at all, Kanamecchi.
I guess the top student of the class doesn't just spend all day studying.
How terrifying.
I spike a yellow ball every day...
But it's okay.
Once we take out their big hitter, Kanamecchi,
we'll have a good chance of winning.
Let's go break his glasses.
Yeah!
Yeah...
Here it comes again, Yukki!
Hey!
I'll get it next time.
Try even looking at it next time!
Here.
Chizuru block!
Score!
Asaba did it!
Wh-What was that?
Yuutan's their big hitter now?
Chizuru-kun!
Okay, I got this—
Why did you run away? You should have got it!
Who could get that?! It would've killed me!
That was dangerous, Yukki!
And that was supposed to be my moment in the spotlight!
Okay, okay. I got it, so serve already.
All right!
Now that we're all up and running,
it's our turn to attack!
Prepare yourselves!
Yeah!
Game, set, and match. Class 1-7 wins.
Sorry.
It just popped! Right off your head!
I'm really not good at sports.
Oh, well.
I'd better go referee the dodgeball game.
Matsushita-kun!
Matsushita-kun! Matsushita-kun!
You're on the Athletics Committee, right?
Come here a second.
The soft tennis referee hasn't shown up?
That's right.
Huh?
Adachi-san from our class was supposed to do it...
Dacchin said she had to leave early.
What?
Can someone take Adachi-san's place?
Yeah, I'll do it.
Yuko, come with me.
Wait for me until I'm finished refereeing.
What? But I have to go cheer for some upperclassmen.
Yocchi, can't you do it?
I can, but...
Noriko, will you wait until I'm done?
I wonder how long it will take...
Anyone will do. Just hurry up!
Aren't you ready yet?
I-I'm sorry.
Satou-san! Satou-san!
What?
The soft tennis referee hasn't turned up.
Can you do it, Satou-san?
Yeah, sure.
Huh? Really?
You decided that quickly.
Yeah, we already lost our dodgeball game, anyway.
The games are on the outside tennis courts, right?
Satou-san! Satou-san! Take this.
It's the game record sheet—
Sitting there tall and dignified all by herself,
Satou-san seemed a little larger...
and a little cooler that day.
You And Me.
Milk
Game, set, and match. Class 3-3 wins, three to two.
Yes, yes, yes!
We're going to the finals!
You're kidding...
Class 3-3's volleyball game?
Yeah.
It was at the same time as our dodgeball game,
so I haven't seen them play yet.
I heard they made it to the finals.
I really want to go see it.
Do you know one of the upperclassmen on the team?
Yeah, s-someone I'm sort of... friends with.
A friend?
Yeah.
I wonder who it could be in Class 3-3...
Maybe Yuuki-senpai is playing, too?
I want to go see that game, too...
Oh, I mean, an upperclassman from my club is...
An upperclassman from the Manga Club might be playing,
so I just... I just figured I should go cheer him on.
I promise that I didn't mean anything else—
Why don't you go watch?
Let's finish this so we can go watch the game.
D-Do you think they jump really high when they attack?
Of course they do!
Way higher than either of us can reach, like this!
They jump this high!
You're right.
Maybe like this.
No, higher!
Maybe this high?
Higher, higher!
This high!
Wipe it off! Wipe it off!
Tissues, tissues, tissues, tissues...
Wh-What are we going to do?
You are awarded this congratulatory letter for your
outstanding performance at Homare High School
More and more schools have stopped assigning ranks at their sports events, you know.
What? Where did that come from?
We can't do that!
We have to hand out awards!
But...
But they're soaking wet!
Let's just get them dried off. It'll be okay.
The volleyball game's starting!
What?!
What are we going to do?
I'm exhausted.
Huh? What are you two doing?
Oh, we just... We got the awards wet.
You did what?
Will everything be okay?
Should I lend you my dryer?
Huh?
I always bring it with me to use after P.E.
Really? That would be a huge help!
Th-Thanks.
No problem.
Oh, right.
I hear you subbed in for the absent referee.
Thanks.
There!
Hey, what are you doing?
What else is wet?
Huh? Oh... just these.
How many of these did you get wet?
Sorry.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
U-Um... Could you take care of this?
Huh?
Satou-san and I want to watch a game.
We know some of the seniors who are playing.
Sure.
We'll do it.
I got to watch my seniors play thanks to you, Satou-san.
They're still playing, right?
Yeah!
It's not over, is it?
No!
We can't get in.
I can't.
Time out.
Why is Yuuki trying so hard?
Who knows?
Yukki, I'm surprised you still have enough energy to attack.
I don't have that much energy.
I'm getting tired.
Tournaments are brutal.
By the time the final match rolls around, I'm out of energy!
But the finals are a sparkling stage.
We don't usually have much luck,
so this will make a nice memory.
Everything's sparkling so much that I can barely see.
Excuse me, but you look like you're about to depart from our world with that memory.
When your turn to serve comes around,
it's like playing Russian roulette.
I know.
They say that important games like these are decided by the first person to make a mistake.
H-Hey, don't say that.
I'm about to serve.
Just take it easy, Shun-chan.
That's right.
I won't blame you even if we come in second place.
What if I mess up?
Sh-Shun-chan!
You can do it!
Masaki-chan?
It's Matsushita-kun.
Hey, Mary.
You got the best seat in the house.
Oh, right! You can't see if you're sitting any lower.
Everyone around you would be too tall.
Shut up!
You! We're in the middle of a match.
If you're not going to serve, I'll give the ball to the other team.
Oh, sorry.
Steady!
Y-You can do it!
He waved to me.
What are they doing, stopping in the middle of a game like that?
I'm glad we got to watch the game.
Yeah.
Th-They're so cool.
A-Amazing!
He jumped so high!
I saw it! He jumped! He jumped really high!
He jumped this high!
No, higher!
Way higher! This high!
Hey, quit playing around and cheer for us.
Now, now, Chizuru-san.
Who cares? They seem to be having fun.
Don't bother. You won't make it.
You shouldn't underestimate the strength of a man
who led his team to victory at the sports festival.
I'm not underestimating you, and you didn't lead us anywhere.
What?! Didn't all of you see my glorious plays?
Why don't you get one in, then?
It all comes down to this one chance. Go ahead.
What?
Why are you setting the bar so high?
You're so mean!
You're the one who set it that high.
Damn it.
Then... Then if I make this, Mary will show up again...
Sh-Shun-chan.
That was quick!
Masaki-chan.
Are you doing something for the Athletics Committee again?
No. Today, I'm the class officer.
You're by yourself again? Isn't that heavy?
I-I'm fine.
Oh, Satou-san?
Are you taking those to the faculty office?
Do you want me to carry half?
I'm on my way to the office, too.
Thanks. Half, then.
Okay.
Be careful.
Remember, you don't have to carry her.
Anyway... Let's pick up where we left off, Chizuru-kun.
Let's see you throw it in.
Ow, my stomach suddenly hurts.
Shun-chan, you do it for me.
What? Me?
One chance. Just one chance!
What?
You're one to talk.
I'm sorta nervous.
You are, aren't you?
It's okay. Go for it!
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "Stripped Bare."
Stripped Bare