Ma-chan, hurry up and eat breakfast.
O-Okay, I'll be right there!
The flowers are blooming.
Buds are appearing on the cherry trees.
Spring will be here soon.
Let's see...
"To our graduates:
Congratulations on graduating.
Those of us who remain will continue...
to pass through these school gates, still not even knowing our way"
Ka-na-mecchi!
Honestly! Even though you're walking to school, you're still studying?
You could run into a telephone pole, you know.
It definitely wasn't a telephone pole that just ran into me.
What's this?
It's what I have to do for the graduation ceremony.
That must be a lot of work.
You said it! You're gonna be cleaning up all by yourself after the graduation ceremony or something?
Kanamecchi, what did you do to deserve that?
That's not what I have to do.
Incumbent student rep: Tsukahara Kaname.
Now this school will be ours.
Who the hell says that?
I feel like I'm going to trip over all the words I don't usually use.
You can do it.
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
You're not going to wear this jacket to the graduation ceremony, are you?
Of course not. I know better.
I'm gonna look sharp at the ceremony.
I've never seen you looking sharp.
That was close.
That wasn't close at all.
He caught you.
It does seem like you'd wear that to the graduation ceremony if he hadn't warned you.
I can see why he felt the need to do it.
But this jacket's my look.
No one cares.
Anyway, the graduation ceremony
Animal Crackers
has nothing to do with us, right?
That's not true.
After the ceremony, first and second years present flowers
to graduating members of their clubs.
Invent flowers?
No, Shun-chan, you're the only one who can
pull flowers out of thin air.
Present flowers.
Well, you're not in any clubs,
so that doesn't really have anything to do with you, either.
It was really interesting.
Really?
By the way, I haven't seen Masaki around lately.
You're right.
Maybe you just haven't seen her because she's so short.
What's wrong?
There she is.
Masaki.
Huh?
Hey.
Chizuru's got cookies.
Come over here.
Stop them.
Why did you pretend you didn't hear us?
You should never turn down sweets. Isn't that right, Chizuru?
Chizuru?
What's wrong?
Um, nothing.
What should I do?
Hey, Mary. Morning.
Do you want some cookies?
Here, take a handful.
Here.
Oh, right. There should be some shaped like sheep in here.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
I'll go get a dustpan and a broom.
Oh, okay.
Mary, it's okay.
Some of them survived.
Here, you can have them.
It's fine.
Since that day, I haven't really spoken to Mary.
I like you, Mary.
What's her problem?
I know it's my fault,
but for her to be so obvious about avoiding me is just...
Just...
A picture?
Well, we're graduating soon.
So we want one to remember them by.
Are you seriously asking him to do this?
It'll be fine.
Just take a picture of Asaba
Yuuta-kun and Yuuki-kun acting normal.
Okay?
Amazing!
Um...
Leave it to me!
I'll get a bunch of shots that'll put the pros to shame!
We just want normal ones...
Yuutan.
Look! Look over here!
Yukki, you too!
Nice, nice, nice!
Here goes!
Yuuta, why is he taking our picture all of a sudden?
Who knows?
Chizuru, why are you—
Hey, come on.
You think you're celebrities just because you're a little popular?
Stop being so touchy just because girls like you.
Chizuru-kun, you're the one being touchy.
Well, prepare yourselves!
Cameraman Chizuru's going to expose the true faces hiding behind your smiling façades.
How terrifying.
Huh? Behind what?
Let's see...
Yuutan, yours came out pretty good,
but you almost seem too nice.
It's like something's missing.
For you, let's see...
Try hitting my viewfinder with an overwhelming aura of negativity!
Very well.
That hand gesture is extremely annoying.
It's that hair.
What?
Try messing up your hair a little.
It just needs a little styling gel.
H-Hey, Chizuru!
Try messing up your shirt, too.
Hey, Yuuki-kun!
Good. That's good, Yuutan!
You're a super handsome man now!
This hair just looks like wet seaweed to me.
Okay! You're next, Yukki!
And then, it's Kanamecchi!
What? Why me?
Our theme is: The school's biggest thug and the class president!
Like this?
No, no, no!
The theme is the school's biggest thug and the class president!
You have to show more animosity for each other!
Then...
"Then," nothing!
Don't actually try to hit me!
I'm just going to lightly punch you for show.
It'll be fine.
You won't even have to worry about your glasses breaking.
You're planning to punch me right in the face with all you've got!
Kaname, you just hit harder than anyone else did.
I can't believe I ran away like that.
They probably think I'm weird.
Okay, Shun-chan, you're next.
Try acting a little naughty.
That's straight up dirty.
My head's all sticky.
Wh-What should I do?
I could go around that way.
But then, it'd be obvious that I'm avoiding them.
I should go this way.
But I don't know what expression I should make.
Oh, it's Mary.
What's up? Are you taking a class trip or something?
I'm a cameraman now!
Do you want me to take your picture, Mary?
N-No, I'm fine.
I see. I guess class is about to start.
Well then...
Well then, I'll take a picture of the two of you.
Huh?
Okay, okay. Stand next to each other.
What? No, you don't have to—
Okay, switching places with the cameraman.
Okay?! This isn't okay!
P-Peace!
Come on, make a peace sign, Mary.
My hands are full.
Then, smile.
Come on, let's see it.
I can't.
My hands are full.
You don't need your hands to smile!
Who cares? Really?
Hey, he's trying to take our picture! Put some feeling into it!
Check your hair in a mirror or something.
Shut up. You're one to talk.
You should look at your own hair in the mirror!
My hair doesn't have anything to do with this!
You're so annoying!
There's always something with you!
You don't have to tell me to make a peace sign!
Okay, okay, fine.
I'm sorry, I'm sure.
I talked to him normally.
How long are you two going to fight?
I'm taking the picture.
Say: "Cheese."
Oh, no.
I totally blinked.
I'll take another one.
Huh? Another?
Just in case.
Yuuki, you're taking too many.
It's such an embarrassing picture.
Well, it's not like anyone will see it.
How did it turn out?
We should be able to see it soon.
How exciting!
Mary?
What's with her?
Mary!
Hey, wait! Mary!
Mary, wait!
Mary!
What are you doing?
No!
Let go!
Everyone's supposed to look at it together.
Hey.
No!
Why are you being so stubborn?
Because I blinked!
I bet my face looks weird!
Huh? You blinked?
Now we really hafta see it—
No! Don't!
I don't want Shun-chan to see it!
Well, I don't think you should show that to anyone, not just Shun-chan.
They'd all laugh.
Shut... up.
I don't want Shun-chan to see it!
Mary's head is always filled with thoughts of Shun-chan.
Only Shun-chan.
Always...
Constantly...
You And Me.
Today, each one of you will spread...
your wings and leave this school...
in pur-pursuit... in pursuit of your dreams.
We will keep that image in our hearts,
as the rest of us stay here and continue our studies.
42nd Homare High Graduation Certificate Awarding Ceremony
In closing, I wish you all the best of health, happiness, and success as you leave our school.
42th Hoki Homare Graduation Certificate Awarding Ceremony
All my heartfelt congratulations to you on this day.
Current student representative: Tsukahara Kaname.
What am I going to do?
Maybe I really should give it back.
I accidentally took the picture where my eyes are open.
Now for the response from the graduating students.
Idiot.
Graduating student rep: Ohno Isao-kun.
Kanamecchi stuttered, didn't he?
Yes.
Huh? I wasn't listening.
I even managed to talk to him normally.
What am I doing?
Tachibana.
The cherry blossoms grow bigger by the day,
Oh, this is—
and on this day, when the warm sunlight heralds the coming of spring,
See me after this is over!
Crap...
You have my sympathy.
we thank you for this grand ceremony.
Idiot.
Also, we thank you for the warm and memorable messages
from the principal, our guests, and the current student representative.
Thank you again.
Three years ago, when we passed through this school's gates...
This concludes the 42nd Homare High School graduation ceremony.
I'll put it in his locker.
He'll definitely notice it if I do that.
Oh, sorry.
E-Excuse me, I—
Ouch.
Excuse me!
Please let me through!
Why are you stumbling around, Mary?
Are you okay?
Hey, Tachibana.
Oh, crap.
I told you to come see me after the ceremony.
Oh, I...
Hey, Tachibana!
Sorry! I'll come see you later!
That was such a nice ceremony.
What, you mean Kaname's stuttering speech?
Shut up.
Hey, where's Chizuru?
The guidance counselor went like this, and this.
So this, this, and this.
Right.
No, he didn't.
If we don't hurry, the graduates will leave.
Hurry up.
They're leaving.
Wait, wait!
I wonder if they'll cry.
You took the wrong photo, didn't you?
Here it is.
You really did blink.
Your face was so funny.
Here.
You really made a weird face.
I can see why you wouldn't want him to see this...
I wonder if the third years are coming out soon.
What...
What should I do?
How should I act?
Act like you always have.
I wasn't asking you for an answer,
and I know you like Shun-chan.
The thing I'd hate most is if you'd stop talking to me altogether.
So...
Yeah.
So,
keep acting like you always have.
B-But what exactly do you mean by "like I always have"?
D-Does that mean I can accept snacks when you offer them—
Oh, come on!
I don't know all the specifics!
I mean why are you even asking me, "What should I do?"
B-Because...
Because I really don't know.
No matter how much I think about it, I don't know.
Mary...
During class, while eating,
when I'm in the bath, after I've gotten into bed.
I can't stop thinking about what I should do.
It's all I think about.
Why are you laughing?
I'm not laughing.
You are!
You... are...
I'm not.
Even if it was just a little...
Even if it was only for a little while, you did think about me a lot.
You filled your head with thoughts of me.
That's enough.
Congratulations!
A picture! Can we get a picture?
It's Shun-chan and the others.
Hey!
Yukki ignored me.
Hey, Yukki!
The flowers are blooming.
Buds are appearing on the cherry trees.
Spring will soon be here.
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "Sugar Baby, Fly Baby."