So cold.
Mary!
Morning!
Good morning.
What? What do you want?
I was just saying hi.
I see.
Hey, um...
Is Shun-chan going to
be eating lunch in the cafeteria today?
Huh? Yeah.
Really?
Okay, see you later.
Chizuru.
What are you doing by the first years' lockers?
Yuuta, leave him alone.
He's finally found the determination to start anew as if it were first year.
I see.
That's not it!
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
That's so good.
Nothing beats a hot bowl of udon in the winter.
Right?
Kaname, can't you look a little happier while you're eating?
You're making my food taste bad.
Shut up.
Whose fault is it that I have to eat convenience store bread?
You can't mess up the bag, Kaname.
point
I haven't taken the sticker off yet.
How many more stickers do you need?
A lot more.
It's your fault for coming up with this "sticker duty" thing, you monkey.
Kanamecchi,
I know you're upset because you don't get to eat your mother's home-made lunch,
but don't take it out on us.
That has nothing to do with this!
Try to keep it down in the cafeteria, you two.
Shun-chan.
Masaki-chan.
Um, have you finished eating?
Yes.
Hey, what did you do to your finger?
It's nothing.
Anyway...
I wanted to show you this.
That's the bear I gave you!
But those clothes...
I tried making him an outfit.
That's amazing, Masaki-chan.
Can I take a look?
Sure.
Huh? Mary made them?
H-Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Ow.
I was just looking at his pants.
I can't help but get the feeling
that you were expecting something to be in his pants.
Santa doesn't keep presents that adults would like in there.
I know that!
Sheesh.
I'm sure the bear loves his new clothes.
I'm glad he does!
Even though no one beckons it,
winter dutifully arrives every year.
Today's another typically cold winter day.
That concludes today's Student Council meeting.
Ugh. It's still raining?
What am I going to do?
Hey.
What are you up to, Shorty?
Don't take someone else's umbrella.
Y-You're wrong! It's the other way around!
Someone stole my umbrella!
You have my sympathies.
Umbrellas get stolen at school all the time.
Your home's in the same direction as mine, isn't it?
Do you want to share with me?
It's fine. Besides, I'm sure you'd...
You'd probably hog the umbrella, anyway.
Like hell I would!
Fine, whatever.
Have fun getting wet, then.
Bye.
H-Hey, wait! What are you doing?
Oh, come on.
It's true.
Whoa, hold up.
Isn't that Satou-san?
Huh?
What? No way!
She's sharing an umbrella with a boy!
Who is it?
Isn't that guy on the Student Council?
What?
No way. How?!
Good morning.
Hey, did you hear?
She was with Tsukahara-senpai from the Student Council...
What? Oh, that?
Good morning, Satou-san.
D-Do you mind if I ask you a weird question?
Satou-san, are you going out with the
second-year student, Tsukahara-senpai?
My friend told me
that she saw you guys sharing an umbrella yesterday
and that you kissed!
Of course we didn't!
What could possibly make you believe we have that kind of relationship?!
Hell would freeze over first!
Wow, his upper limit is Kaori-sensei, and his lower limit is Masaki?
Your playing field's too wide, Senpai.
I can't even tell where the foul line is.
Who are you calling "Senpai"?
Are you stupid?
I-It didn't happen! It didn't happen, Shun-chan!
I didn't want to go, but Kaname forced me to...
You forced her?
Does that make you a dangerous individual,
like a street slasher?
Hey Shorty, stop saying things that'll give them the wrong idea!
Listen up!
She said she had something in her eye,
so I just leaned down to check!
Right. Everyone makes up their own excuses.
Believe me, Shun-chan! It's a misunderstanding! Completely wrong!
It's not an excuse—
You're dead!
You have some guts to think
I'd let you get away with kissing Mary!
You're not Kanamecchi any more, you're Kana-messed up!
Won't any of you listen to me?!
Is it this mouth?
Is this the mouth you used to kiss Mary?
Let me have it too...
Hey, what's going on over here?
Homeroom's about to—
Huh?
I heard you were dating Satou-san, but...
I see.
You're wrong on both counts!
I can't believe I got so carried away.
Now that I think about it,
there's no way you'd go for Mary.
Kanamecchi, you already have your mom and Kaori-sensei.
No, I don't.
I suppose I'll make an exception
and forgive you for sharing that umbrella.
Chizuru-san, making exceptions doesn't really count as forgiving.
Jeez, this is ridiculous.
Now, now. Winter vacation's coming up.
I'm sure the rumors will disappear over the break.
Right?
Chizuru, why do you seem so happy?
Hey, Christmas isn't long after the beginning of the break.
Let's all do something fun on Christmas!
What? It'll be cold, though.
Hey! Don't be so glum!
The city's already alive with the sound of jingle bells, jingle bells!
Then I'll lie around at home, laughing all the way.
Christmas is just... If you take a nap near the heater, you wake up and it's already over.
Your lives as young men are over.
What's wrong with you?
Why won't you hang out with us?
It's not like...
It's not like any of us have girlfriends!
Someone hold me all night!
If you're going to cry, don't yell at us about it!
You And Me.
Damn it. They're all so cold.
If I had a girlfriend, I'd have a present or two.
This is so cute!
It really is!
I bet you'd look good in this.
Maybe I'll get it.
Is this really what girls like?
I bet this would look good on Mary.
Oh, man. She's too cute.
Really? You'll buy this for me?
Sure. It's almost Christmas.
I'm so happy. Thank you!
No, no, no. No way.
I could never get her a present.
I know it's Christmas, but there's no way something good like that would...
Look at this. This hair ribbon is so cute.
You're right.
Huh?
I-I bought it.
Maybe I made a mistake.
Yeah, but... but...
Spots... Stripes...
Spots...
Stripes!
Spots!
Hey. Are you shopping, too, Mary?
What a coincidence.
Don't go, "Hey!" at me! You scared me!
I-Is Shun-chan with you?
No, I'm here by myself.
I see.
That'll be 525 yen.
Oh, um...
Could you gift wrap it, please?
Very well.
Hey, Mary.
This is just a guess,
but that's not a Christmas present for Shun-chan, is it?
A girl giving a guy a present?
Don't you think that's a little weird?
I-It's not weird.
It's not a Christmas present.
He gave me a bear key chain at the summer festival,
and he's always helping me study.
I-It's to thank him!
So it's fine if I give this to him!
Fine, fine.
That's a stretch.
What the heck?
It's been raining so much lately.
It's December. Where's the snow?
What am I going to do?
I didn't bring an umbrella.
You shouldn't do that.
Just so you know, I don't have a handkerchief.
I never expected you to have one.
Wait. What kind of impression do you have of me?
That sort of impression.
I see.
Mary, this...
You two.
Yes?
You make a cute couple.
No! We're not a couple!
I only have one umbrella,
but would you like to use it?
Really? Are you sure?
Thank you, then.
Is that what we look like?
Looks like there are still some nice people in the world.
Sharing an umbrella.
Come on. Get under.
Mary?
I'm fine.
You're fine? You're not getting under it?
But she gave us this—
If someone starts another weird rumor,
Shun-chan will get the wrong idea again.
With Kanamecchi, people saw you
because you were near the school.
We're pretty far from the school here,
so it'll be fine.
Here, come on.
You don't need to be so worried about rumors, anyway.
Shun-chan won't care either way.
W-Wait. That's not what I mean. I just...
Mary, wait!
Take the umbrella.
How many more days until spring break?
Chizuru-san, you just casually skipped an entire season.
I've had just about enough of winter.
My body and soul are plenty cold!
It hasn't even snowed yet this year.
Oh, right.
All the lovey-dovey couples of the world
are accelerating global warming with their steamy flirting!
Love's supposed to save the world,
so I'm not sure that's it.
What's wrong with you?
Winter vacation starts tomorrow.
What happened to your long-awaited Christmas?
Oh, it's Masaki.
Oh, Shorty.
What are you doing?
I-I didn't see Shun-chan in Class 5,
so I thought he might be here.
Shun? He's not here.
Is that a Christmas present for Shun?
Of course.
Today's your last chance to give this to him.
Hey, it's none of your business! Give it back!
Lucky you, Tsukahara.
Is that a Christmas present from this girlfriend I've heard about?
What? I told you she's not my—
What'd she give you? Let's see.
You idiot! That's not for me!
You shouldn't take people's presents
just because you're jealous.
Get out of here.
Come on.
You're not curious, Tachibana?
Here.
The ribbon's just a little crooked.
Nothing's wrong with the present inside.
Yeah.
Welcome back.
What did Masaki want?
The lights came on.
It's beautiful.
You guys really like that kind of thing, don't you?
Who cares about some stupid decoration?
Shut up. You boys wouldn't get it.
Cute decorations like this are exciting.
Mary!
Why are you going home?
Wh-Who are you?
"Who am I"? I'm Chizuru.
Why are you going home?
What about Shun-chan's present?
You haven't given it to him.
B-But the ribbon's all messed up.
Here.
Now it's all good.
Come on, come on.
Go, go, go.
Go on. Go on.
Stop it, you pervert!
So cold.
I gave it to him.
What'd he say?
"Thanks."
That's great.
Hey...
What are you doing?
Here, I got it.
Oh, sorry.
Thanks...
for the ribbon.
If you...
don't have an umbrella, you can share mine.
If you have your own...
N-No! I don't!
I don't! I totally didn't bring one today!
Just wait here! My bag!
I'll go get my bag, so wait here!
Don't leave!
All right!
Viva Christmas!
Hurry up and get here, my spring!
But just for now, stop right here,
for my winter with you.
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "Very Christmas."