Where am I?
Huh?
Mary?
What? You have a present for me?
I'm so happy!
What are you giving me?
Wait, Mary!
Stop, stop, stop!
No!
Men... Men are so...
I'm sorry, Mary.
Just kidding!
Why would a young wolf like me be sorry?
I wanna see the rest, the rest...
Wait! There's no time for that!
I definitely can't be late today.
Valentine's Day
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
Valentine's Day
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
Finished.
I managed to finish in time.
I hope Shun-chan likes them.
Kaname-kun...
Good morning.
This guy's already had some chocolate, and it's still so early!
Shut up! It was from my mom.
I'll eat it when I get home.
Let go. Seriously, I'll be late to school.
So what? I'm being serious, too.
Really serious.
You're only making it harder for me to eat it!
Fine. I guess I should just throw it in the trash, then.
Sorry for giving you so much trouble this morning.
The way you pout like that is what gives me the most trouble!
Fine, whatever!
Okay, it's delicious.
I'm off.
Kaname-kun.
Unbelievable.
Who cares about Valentine's Day, anyway?
It's cute...
Going overboard for the people you love.
That's right.
If you can't understand women, you'll always be a child.
I am her child.
Stop acting like we're lovers.
Oh, that's right...
Today's Valentine's Day, isn't it?
Why don't we all have some chocolate at lunch break?
Shun, when did you become a teenage girl?
Huh?
Azuma-sensei, have this.
I'm serious, don't ya know?
Th-Thank you.
Man, what are you saying?
See you later, Sensei.
Azuma-sensei, you're so lucky!
How can you have so much already while we have none?!
They say teachers are always role models for their students.
Way to go.
But these chocolates don't really mean much. NThey're just to show appreciation for my work.
There you go again. You're always so modest.
You sure did get a lot.
Can you eat all of those by yourself?
Yes. I'm happy to receive them, so I'll eat them all.
You'll eat every last morsel, and leave no one behind?
And leave not one behind.
Yeah, yeah. Whatever you say.
Today is Valentine's Day.
A day for boys and girls to pretend
that they don't notice how nervous everyone else is feeling...
"Pretend"?
There he is.
Matsuoka-kun, Yuuta-kun.
Takahashi-san?
All the girls in class got together and made some chocolate.
It's not much, but...
Oh, thank you.
Thanks.
Well, that's... every... thing.
Oh, yes. Thank you for specially giving us some.
No, everyone got a pack.
Everyone's going on about chocolate this,
and chocolate that, and chocolate chococochoco!
You can't even say it anymore.
I don't care!
A bitter man ignores events like this
and focuses on his studies.
Right, Yukki?
Huh? Someone decorated my pencil case.
Like hell they did!
Yukki, you got a ton of chocolate, too!
Damn it!
Ow, ow.
Lucky guy. I want some chocolate, too.
I wonder if Mary's gonna give Shun-chan chocolate.
But maybe... just maybe...
Maybe she'll give me some, too.
Maybe the dream I had this morning was a premonition or something...
H-Hey, Mary-san.
What's up? You seem really tired.
Yeah. I've been practicing making truffles every night.
Masaki-chan, have you not been getting enough sleep?
Did something happen?
No, I'm just super duper!
I see.
Hey.
Yes, yes. What is it?
Well, uh... um...
Do you think Shun-chan likes... s-sweet things?
Yeah, he does.
I wonder what's wrong...
Anything else? Are you all set?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Huh...
Kaname-kun, you seem down.
I was just thinking about how my mom's going to force me to eat
all that chocolate cake she made when I get home.
Just thinking about it gives me heartburn.
Kaname, since you're an only child, you get all of the love your mother has to offer.
It would be different if you had a younger brother.
Why don't you tell your mom you want a kid?
Like hell I will!
That means something completely different!
D-Did you get any chocolate today, Shun-chan?
What? I never get any.
My mother or sister just give me some every year.
U-Um, excuse me.
I-It's a chocolate tart.
I made it myself, so it's not very...
I'm sure it's not any good, but...
W-Well, um... If you're not...
dating anyone right now...
No, no. This is, u-um...
What? Come on.
Don't hide it.
She was from another school, wasn't she?
Way to go, Shun. She was all over you.
N-No, that's not it. Please stop.
Show us what's inside.
H-Hey, wait.
Good for you. Does it really bother you that much?
Huh? Well, I...
I'm happy, but...
Wow. It's a homemade tart.
It looks delicious.
Hey, don't open it!
Mary.
Mary!
Ma—
Hey!
What are you doing?
Is that what I think it is?
Aren't those for Shun—
You try one!
What do you think you're—
See?
They taste weird, don't they?
They don't taste any good, do they?
I know! I'll buy something from the convenience store, and...
Hey, wait! Wait—
Calm down.
Mary!
A-Are you okay, Mary? Mary!
Excuse me. Can you return our ball, please?
Hold on, Mary!
Don't die on me!
L-Lack of sleep?
She doesn't have a fever.
She'll be fine once she gets some rest.
I see.
Why'd you have to fall over so dramatically?
I have to step out for a minute.
Can you walk Satou-san home if she wakes up?
I'm a little worried about her.
Ah, sure.
She doesn't even have a test coming up.
I wonder what she was working so hard on...
You And Me.
Huh? Where am I?
Wait, when did I fall asleep?
Um...
Mary, are you sure you can...
What time is it?
What am I going to do? I didn't give Shun-chan any chocolate.
I need to go to the convenience store and buy some...
No, Shun-chan must have gone home already.
It's over.
It's okay.
Even if you can't give him anything today,
you can still give him something tomorrow.
Okay?
You should have given him the chocolate you made.
They were good.
Hey, Mary.
Come on, Mary...
Hey, did you really give that teacher some chocolate?
I was so nervous.
You did it?
Yeah.
What am I doing?! What am I doing?! What am I doing?!
I'm impressed you can eat so many sweets.
Haven't you been eating all of that chocolate you got yesterday?
Mm, yeah.
Mm?
Yuuki, you'd better give them some on White Day in return.
I don't think I'll have any left by then.
Not those.
Shun, Chizuru, do you guys want some...
What's wrong with them?
They've been like that since this morning.
Who knows?
I wanna die.
Why did I do that yesterday?
What am I going to do when I see her again?
Oh, but Mary's body was so soft.
No, I shouldn't think about that.
Oh, looks like Chizuru's fine.
He's obviously not!
Shun.
Yes?
What happened after that girl
confessed her feelings to you yesterday?
Her cell number was on the card, wasn't it?
Oh, um... I haven't...
messaged her yet.
You haven't?
She doesn't go to our school.
If you don't text her, she...
That girl was pretty amazing.
It's not easy going to another school by yourself.
I-I'm sorry.
I guess you don't know what to do when a stranger
suddenly hands you chocolate.
But we cross paths most mornings.
You even picked up my train pass for me once.
U-Um, I have things to do, so I... I'm going home.
Oh. Sure.
Is he going to be okay?
It's probably the first time anyone's confessed their feelings to Shun before.
I bet he doesn't know what to do.
You're probably right.
He's been standing there all day just thinking.
What do you mean, "probably"?
You should be helping him with his problem or something.
Shun prefers to think for
himself when he has a decision to make.
Ow...
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
I see.
I was convinced something was wrong.
"Something"?
With your beloved Mary-chan.
What? How did you know?
How? I can tell by looking at you.
So what happened?
Nothing.
What are they doing?
Nothing happened!
Come on. Why don't you tell Big Brother Yuuki?
Come on, come on, come on.
Cut it out, Yukki.
Yukki, you'd better not fall in love with her, too.
Chizuru, where are you going?
I'm going home!
What's his problem?
I won't.
EVERYTHING
Shun-chan.
Shun-chan doesn't live in this direction.
Where's he going?
Sorry, Shun-chan.
Who's that?
Isn't he from another school?
Um, is something wrong?
I was so surprised to see you standing at the gates.
S-Sorry for showing up unannounced.
Oh, no. That's not what I meant.
Um, well...
Wh-What am I going to do?
Something big is going down.
What are you up to?
Mary!
Shun-chan isn't with you?
You're spying on him? I can't believe you!
I get it, so pipe down.
I'm sorry.
I can't go out with you.
I see.
Oh, it's fine.
Um, I didn't really think it would work out, so I...
I'm sorry, I guess.
But I was happy.
I was really happy.
The chocolate tart was delicious.
Thank you.
I'm happy you came all the way to my school to meet me.
You okay with this?
I mean, I guess that's not what I really mean, but...
Shun-chan was always so nice.
I always believed he would happily accept how I feel.
I thought every day after that would be so fun and full of happiness...
But for the first time,
I began to think he might not accept my feelings, after all.
I was so afraid and uncertain...
that I couldn't work up the courage to do it.
It was delicious.
Thank you.
I couldn't do it.
A leaf.
Huh? Oh.
Eye!
"Eye"? What are you...
Huh? You've never made an eye shape before?
Sure. In elementary school.
I'm the left eye.
Huh? Then, I'm...
the right eye?
You're way too short for this.
What do you mean by that?!
I only did it because you did!
My evening with you unfolds before my eyes.
Blindingly bright and overwhelmingly happy.
And somewhere deep inside, really frustrated.
I like you, Mary.
Huh? Wait, Mary-san...
Are you mad?
Why did you have to say that?
I mean, you're you.
What?
I'm so happy.
So happy that I could gush tears.
So happy that I could overflow with smiles.
I'm happy that I love you.
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "Us Boys."
Us Boys