Students don't have any money.
The money we receive at New Year's
disappears with the melting winter snow,
and our meager daily allowance whittles down to zero
from the moment it's put into our hands.
Coin Return
Are you stupid?!
You paid 100 yen for tea?!
Who cares what I buy?
If you're gonna buy anything,
you should get juice like normal people.
Right?
What a waste of money.
Instead of buying that from a vending machine, you could have had some at home for free.
In the end, Kaname thinks he can even buy love with his money.
I bet he thinks there's nothing he can't buy.
Huh?
Haven't we had this conversation before?
This is what you call "smart shopping."
Look. You can sample many fruits in one carton:
Mixed juice!
Delicious Fruit Mix
Who cares what I buy with my own money?
It has nothing to do with you.
How high and mighty you are, Kaname-kun.
I can't even afford juice.
Huh? Yuuki-kun, aren't you going to buy some juice?
Yuuki's broke at the moment.
Oh, what am I going to do?
I won't be able to buy First Fantasy.
It comes out next week.
Yuuki-kun.
Why don't you get a part-time job?
Huh?
A job?
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
A job?
Yes.
Kaname will?
No, you.
You want me to work?
We're almost third years now.
This might be your last chance to get a job before you're too busy with entrance exams.
That's a great idea! You should do it, Yukki.
No way.
I'm not good with customers.
Dealing with customers is a piece of cake!
All you have to do is smile.
Welcome.
How many in your party?
Just like that, right?
Table for one?
I see. Nobody to eat with, huh?
Like that, you mean?
You're not supposed to laugh about it.
I wonder what kind of job would fit Yuuki-kun.
Wait. I didn't say I was gonna—
Okay, okay!
Let's have a strategy meeting to decide on Yukki's job!
I think he'd do well in a bookstore.
Yuuki-kun likes manga.
Animaga
Bargain
books
Well, I guess it'd be nice to read all the new magazines for free.
Uh, the employees can't just stand there and read the books.
How about sitting instead?
It's not about how you read it.
I bet they have lots of cute little picture books.
Yeah, like "Shun-chan in Wonderland."
I can see that.
Isn't working in a fast food place a common part-time job?
No, no.
This guy wouldn't earn anything for his smile.
He won't even smile for money.
Hey, I'd smile if I knew someone was going to pay me for it.
Your smile is so shady.
That's just not you, Yukki.
You should do something like...
Everyone else here is just a customer to me.
But you're different.
Oh, my.
Here, have these.
He's gotta be a host!
Hey, lady killer.
A-A night worker?
Two million yen a night is tough to argue with.
Two million?
That's more money than I can even understand having.
Yeah, just having a thousand yen makes you feel rich.
Hey, don't you guys want to make some money?!
High schoolers can't do jobs like that.
Delivering newspapers.
That's it!
A first job should always be delivering newspapers!
But I want to sleep in as late as I can.
No, no.
He's gotta be a host of the night.
Right, Yukki?
I'd rather just sleep at night.
Forget about working. Do you even want to be alive?
It's fine, really.
I won't get a job.
But Yuuki, if you don't find work, you can't buy your game.
Are you okay with that?
That's right, Yukki.
Yuuki-kun, just give it a go.
Okay?
Fine.
Time to work for my game.
Kaname, I mean.
I told you, you're the one who has to work.
That's how 17-year-old Asaba Yuuki got the first job of his life.
I'm going to eat until I burst today!
Wanna start at one end of the menu and go through it all?
Let's do it!
Thank you for waiting.
May I take your order?
I'd like the hamburger demi-glace, the seafood curry,
the pudding parfait, and a milk tea.
I'd like the steak, the doria, the cheesecake, and a royal milk tea.
The royal milk tea comes iced or hot.
Which would you prefer?
Oh, actually...
Instead of all that, can we just get two black coffees?
You can get your coffees at the drink bar.
Will that be all right?
Uh, yes.
Very well.
The drink bar is over there. Enjoy.
Who was that?!
He's so hot.
Ah, Asaba-kun.
Take this special mixed juice to the customers at A-6.
Okay.
I'm tired.
I thought that if I worked during the week, there'd be less customers and I would have more free time.
Excuse me.
Can I get some water?
Why is it so busy?
Excuse me.
Can I get some here, too?
Excuse me, waiter.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your special mixed juice...
You're working hard, Yukki-kun.
What are all of you doing here?
"What are we doing"?
We were wondering how you were doing,
so we came to see you.
You guys are terrible.
How's work?
I might quit.
It's hard.
Hang in there! It's still your first day.
You'd get a reputation as a quitter if you just resign now.
We saw you taking orders.
I thought you'd be washing dishes in the back.
Well, they said I'd be working in the back when I was interviewed,
but my manager told me to work the floor today.
Hey, what's your manager like? Is she pretty?
There you go again.
No, not even close...
Ow.
Asaba, why are you taking a break?
Manager.
Um, sir...
What?
I'm supposed to be a dishwasher.
What are you, stupid?
With your looks, you should be working the floor.
You're more of a gang boss than a manager.
What?
Nothing.
Are you guys Asaba's friends?
Have you eaten already?
I-I'm sorry! We don't have very much money.
We'll probably only order drinks.
Sorry for being such bad customers.
Why are you apologizing?
Order whatever you want.
In here, the customers are gods.
What?
Take your time.
The Boss is scary.
Th-The manager is scary. He's terrifying!
The Godfather.
He seems like a pretty dependable manager to me.
Maybe he'll be able to make Yuuki...
Welcome.
Yukki, work hard.
Work hard, you say?
You guys are casually ordering drinks while I'm working.
Your encouragement doesn't mean anything.
What's this? A treat from Yukki?
What?
No, you ordered that.
You must really love mixed juice.
What?
We haven't ordered anything yet.
What? Then this is...
This is ridiculous.
How long does it take to make a single mixed juice?
It's still not ready yet?
Maybe he accidentally took it to another table.
You can't be serious.
Hey!
This isn't ours!
Why did you have to drink it, Chizuru?
Why did you bring it to us?
Y-You should sincerely apologize to your manager
and make those customers a new mixed juice.
I can't do that.
If the manager finds out, he'll dock my pay.
That's right. If we're not careful...
What? You drank someone else's juice?
He'll kill us!
You only care about yourselves.
But...
What are we gonna do?
I know.
Yuuki-kun, you have an idea?
I'm going back to work.
Hold on! Don't you dare run from this!
I'm not.
If I'm not out on the floor, I'll look even more suspicious.
But weren't you just heading towards the locker room?
I'll look suspicious if I walk around outside in these clothes.
I have to go change.
You're not thinking of going home, are you?
Okay, okay. Fine.
Let's go secretly prepare another mixed juice.
Yuuta-kun.
Huh? What?
You And Me.
Stop it, Sacchan.
Don't kick your feet like that.
Mind your manners when you're eating.
See?
What cute shoes.
You should wear them so you don't lose them.
Th-Thank you.
Not at all.
Yuuta-kun's so cool.
Yuutan's looking good.
He looks just like me in those clothes.
No, he doesn't.
His work ethic's nothing like yours.
Okay, while Yuuta's pretending to be me,
let's prepare that mixed juice.
Us, too? What are you...
I see.
You can make a mixed juice at the drink bar.
But it's called a special mixed juice
because there's something special in it, right?
Won't she find out?
She might,
but I get the feeling she'll be nice about it,
instead of getting mad.
Yuuki-kun, you have so much faith in your customers.
Look.
How does it take this long to make a mixed juice?
She kinda looks like Anpanda.
I don't believe this!
This is infuriating!
I think she might be surprisingly nice.
She's gonna be pissed.
He was so hot.
Thank you very much.
What do you want to go eat now?
Steak!
Hurry up.
Excuse me.
Yes, I'll be right there.
This isn't bad.
It's good. It's pretty good.
Let's see if we can get even closer to the real thing.
Let's try to bring out the thickness of the juice
with some corn starch!
That'll only turn it into mapo tofu.
Kaname-kun, Chizuru-kun.
I found some good ingredients.
Try using this.
These smell like weeds.
Cafés usually garnish their drinks with some kind of plant.
Where did you get this?
I can't wait much longer!
Don't actually put grass in here.
This isn't garnish. It's a weed.
I see. They say you taste with your eyes first.
You can't taste this!
Honestly... Hey, Shun. Say something.
Don't add more!
But, isn't it cute like a tropical juice?
What are you guys doing?
You can't serve this to anyone.
So mean.
You're oppressing art!
How is this art?
Oh, crap!
Excuse me, Manager!
She's calling for an employee!
It's the manager, of all people!
Wh-What are we going to do?
We don't have time to make a new one.
Calm down, Shun-chan!
I'll go buy some mixed juice from school.
Chizuru, calm down.
Hey, isn't there any way to do this besides the drink bar?
Then how about this?
I'll go to the kitchen and get a blender and some ingredients.
You should've done that in the first place!
Honestly! How long are you going to make us wait for a mixed juice?
I'm terribly sorry.
I'll go get you one immediately.
That won't be necessary! Let's go, Kubota-san!
Please wait.
Excuse me.
Here's your special mixed juice.
Orange
Pardon me. Please watch your feet.
Hey! What are you doing?
I wanted to give our customers freshly-made juice.
What?
WHITE
PEACH
You've already got a complaint on your first day.
I'm docking your pay as of your next shift—
Um, Manager!
I'm sorry. This is Yuuki-kun's first job.
I'm sorry for all the trouble he's caused today.
But he'll work even harder from now on.
Could you please wait to cut his pay until you see how he performs in the future?
Please.
Orange
W-Well, if you insist.
Y-Yeah.
Here we go.
Hey, wai—
Dry cleaning the customer's clothes: 3,900 yen.
The mixed juice you drank and then splattered from the blender: 840 yen.
That's 4,740 yen I'm deducting from your pay.
And you're fired.
Naturally, after that, you have no pay left.
Isn't there at least a few hundred yen left after all those deductions?
No, there isn't.
And even if there was anything left, I'd give it
to your brother, not you.
Um, I'm sorry for switching places with him.
Jeez, you were a worthless employee.
You couldn't even smile for the customers.
If you look for work again,
find something better suited to you.
I think there's plenty of jobs out there that you're suited for
more than running a family restaurant, too.
You can think of this as an expensive learning experience.
Earning money isn't easy, Asaba-kun.
Even high school kids get fired without a second thought these days.
Don't blame it on the times.
Yuuki-kun, failure breeds success.
I'm sure this will help you in the future.
I won't be getting another job for a while.
Well, it wasn't all bad.
You earned some experience points.
I'd rather have money than experience points.
Students don't have any money.
My first job disappeared in my manager's rage.
Because I didn't end up making any money,
the game I wanted slipped even further from my grasp.
Excuse me.
Are you the person who picked up my shoe in the restaurant?
What?
It was you!
I felt like I was Cinderella.
Huh?
Because... Because...
You were so wonderful, like a prince.
What? A prince?
I don't know what you're...
Huh? Yukki...
Thank you.
Sacchan, what are you doing?
Let's go.
Hey, Yukki-san... Did she just kiss you?
No.
No, no. I know she did.
No, she didn't.
She totally did.
Yukki, you just lost your kissing virginity!
Good going, man.
You got the best reward a man could ask for.
She didn't kiss me.
Yuuki, I'll buy you some lemon candy.
Then it'll taste like lemons.
She didn't kiss me!
Isn't work fun, Yukki?
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "Cherry."