I thought growing older would turn me into an adult.
Kou-chan,
how do I look?
You laughed!
Suits really aren't your thing.
I thought I'd get a job, get married,
and somehow become an adult version of myself.
But nothing like that happened.
Come on, everyone! Peace signs!
Hey, cut it out.
What?
Even though I've grown older,
I feel like nothing's changed.
I've still never truly felt like I've become an adult.
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
I smell a perfect crime.
At the time of the crime,
this room was completely locked down.
There are no traces of a weapon or fingerprints.
Then how did the victim die?
This bookcase...
Didn't they say that the victim frequented the library?
Yeah.
Take a look at this book.
Hey, what are they talking about?
There's nothing unusual about it.
We examined that one as well as this one,
but the book the victim borrowed from the library last week...
Huh?
Hey! What's going on?
Shut up already!
How many times have you asked that since we started watching?
Just shut up and watch.
I wouldn't understand anything if I didn't ask.
Telling you would just make me lose track of what's happening.
I'd lose track...
I'd lose...
What are you doing?!
Come on!
Just shut up and watch, monkey!
He's right, Chizuru-kun.
It's about to get really interesting.
I can't hear anything over the noise you guys are making.
I'm going to rewind it a bit.
You are the culprit, Ikegami-san!
Wh-Where's your proof?
Sorry, I fast-forwarded.
Well, that's that.
The mystery's been solved. Clap, clap, clap, clap, clap.
I guess this movie was a miss.
This group's a miss!
Whose bright idea was it to watch movies at my place on Christmas Eve?!
But we don't have the money to go out.
And you have the biggest TV.
DETECTIVE HIGASHITAMA
What should we do now?
We've watched all the DVDs we rented.
We'll go rent some more, of course!
This'll be our DVD Christmas!
Our Christmas Eve's just getting started!
Don't count on sleeping tonight!
Especially you, Kanamecchi!
You better not talk during the movies this time.
Let me just watch in peace.
Um, let's watch the next one without any interruptions.
Step Street
Three, two, one...
Did it come out well?
Okay, let's switch up the order.
Huh? Where's Kanamecchi?
The next theme is: pose like a maiden in love!
You gotta be in the photo with us.
We already got our DVDs.
We're done here.
Let's go already.
Now, now.
I don't...
Come on, come on.
Kanamecchi, throw up some peace signs with us!
Oh, how cute.
Like hell I will.
Why do we have to take these pictures, anyway?
Say "cheese!"
I bet you've never done this before.
Three, two, one...
All the cool kids are doing it.
You're behind the times if you don't use photo booths.
You're the one who's behind the times for calling us "cool kids."
Get ready for the next one.
Peace signs, everyone!
Kaname-kun, aren't you going to do it?
Oh, how cute.
What? You're terrible, Kanamecchi.
Say "cheese."
Fine.
Three, two, one...
Kaname, you're so embarrassing.
The Student Council's gonna have a physical assault case on their hands.
Whose fault is that?
Can't we get a nice picture together?
You can scribble on them too!
We're supposed to choose from these?
This one's pretty good.
What does this button do?
Skin whitening?
Does this one make our eyes bigger?
Let's try it.
I'll be outside.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Azuma-sensei.
Huh? Azuma-sensei? Where?
Azuma-sensei!
Oh, Tachibana-kun. And the rest of you, too.
Buy us some pork buns!
Show us growing boys some love!
Pork buns won't make you any taller!
Where have you been?
A store over there.
Their croquettes looked good.
Don't just disappear like that.
That's the guy from the culture festival.
The festival...
Choco-Banana!
Choco-Banana? What's he talking about?
Who knows?
What are you doing here?
I can go wherever I want.
What are you guys doing here?
We came to rent some—
Shun-chan, you don't have to answer him.
Not only did he cut ahead of me in line at the culture festival,
but this jerk also insulted my height!
You did that?
Who cares? It's all in the past.
I care!
We don't really know what's going on here.
Azuma-sensei, how do you know him?
Oh, right.
I wanted to tell you at the festival, but I guess I forgot.
He's my friend.
I'm Akira!
Are you guys Kou-chan's students?
Your friend?
Kou-chan?
We went to the same high school.
Homare High School.
I'm your Senpai!
What?!
Azuma-sensei, you went to Homare High School?
Yes, actually.
So this guy's the same age as you?
I thought he was around our age.
I know, right?
I've got a baby face,
so people always think I'm younger than I am.
Your face isn't the only reason people think you're young.
Since I'm your Senpai, I expect you to show me some respect.
Especially you, little dude.
Don't call me little!
I see.
You were taking some pictures together.
Oh, Sensei. Do you want one of our pictures?
Are you sure?
Stick it on your phone so that you can always watch over your precious students.
Hey, no fair.
Give me one to put on my phone!
No way!
I bet you'd stick it on a voodoo doll!
I wouldn't do that.
By the way, you're looking rather dapper today, Sensei.
Yeah.
I was at the wedding of a friend from school.
Getting married on Christmas Eve sounds wonderful.
Right? Apparently, they met at work.
What about you, Azuma-sensei?
Are you gonna marry someone you meet at work?
Maybe.
Maybe? Azuma-sensei...
Don't tell us you see your own students that way.
That's not what I meant.
Akira-san, what do you do for a living?
Huh? Me?
I'm Santa Claus.
A black-hearted Santa dressed in all red would make kids cry.
Well, my shift's starting soon.
Don't ignore me!
Akira-san's kinda cute, isn't he?
He's an adult, but he talks like a small child.
I'm pretty sure he actually is a small child.
He said something about being Santa,
but I bet he's just a jobless bum.
I bet he ran away so he wouldn't have to admit that he's broke.
Well, I should get going.
This will probably be the last time I see you boys this year,
so have a happy New Year.
Oh, right. Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
We should go too.
I'm getting cold.
You're right.
He got us the pork buns,
so let's pick up our DVD Christmas where we...
What's wrong?
Are you lost?
Did you fall?
Is that your balloon?
I was holding the string, but it still flew away!
Is that right?
All right!
We'll get your balloon for you.
"We"?
Yukki, gimme a lift!
Just a little further.
You can do it, guys!
Let's grab it and get going already.
Then why don't you help them?
He said he'd get it himself.
Yukki, hold it steady!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Don't drop me.
Don't drop me, even if you lose your balance.
"Don't drop me," you say?
Hey idiot, I'm not playing around!
Seriously, don't drop me!
"Seriously, don't drop me," you say?
I just told you! I'm not kidding.
Huh? What are you guys doing?
Um... the balloon...
Akira-san?
What? Choco-Banana?
Hey Chizuru, if you keep squirming like that, I really will...
You And Me.
Um, why are we dressed like this?
It's the least you can do after ruining our event.
You're going to repay us with hard work.
Of course.
With you guys around,
not only is it impossible to watch DVDs undisturbed,
but now I can't even watch them at all.
Is this a woman's costume?
Our Christmas Eve plans!
What did you guys think you were doing?
Shut up!
What do you think you're doing?
You shouldn't go cosplaying around the city, you bum!
How rude.
I'm not playing around. This is my job.
Right?
Akira-chan, if you had gotten here earlier it might not have happened!
Thanks for helping us out again.
We even hired a reindeer this year.
Hey!
Akira-san, is it possible for you to act your age?
Thank you.
Mom, Santa gave me a new balloon.
Make sure you hold on tight this time.
Okay.
Not to Yuuta's hand.
Those twins sure are popular.
Well, sorry for not being as popular as them!
What're you talking about?
Looks like you guys are really popular too,
if you know what I mean.
Shut up!
His hair's weird!
I wonder if we can see her panties.
Can you see them?
Stop it!
You're shaking the ladder!
Santa's scared.
U-Um, excuse me.
Can you do something about these kids for me?
Hey!
Real reindeer aren't on great terms with Santa, are they?
Sensei.
Sensei?
You're right.
Sensei, Sensei.
Yes, yes. Hold on.
Ch-Choco-Banana, are you an elementary school teacher?
Of course not. I'm Santa Claus.
Here you go. One for each of you.
Yeah, but they just...
It's Santa.
It's the real Santa!
Merry Christmas!
Santa's got a present for all you good little kids.
What about the reindeer? Where are the reindeer?
Oh, my reindeer like to run free.
Don't talk about the reindeer like they're dogs.
I know. I'll give you one of my caramels, Santa.
It's really good.
Thank you.
Nonta, you're such a baby.
There's no way he's the real Santa.
Huh?
He's just a normal guy dressed up like Santa.
What?
You're wrong! He's the real Santa!
He's even got a white beard.
That's right. D-Don't say such things...
But that Santa Claus isn't even fat.
Even Santa is trying to get in shape these days.
Right, Santa?
Choco-Banana, what are you doing?!
Are you stupid?
Why did you do that?!
It'll be fine.
It was just one caramel.
I'm not talking about the sugar!
Whatever, just put the beard back on!
The caramel will get stuck to it.
Oh, right. I still haven't given you your present.
Liar.
Huh?
I don't want your present!
Wait, you dropped your caramels!
What a careless kid.
Yeah.
But at least his carelessness is a million times cuter than yours.
Step Street
I'm exhausted. I've had enough of this.
Kaname-kun, you skipped out on us.
No, I didn't.
The event's almost over, so they said I could take a break.
Huh? Really? It's over?
Chizuru, you seem to be more worn out than the rest of us.
Of course I am.
I've been with the living eighth wonder of the world.
There you are.
Good work, boys.
We'll take care of the rest, so you can go home.
Seriously?!
Thank you for all your help.
You can help yourselves to some
of the left over giveaway candy.
Really? Really?!
First come, first serve.
Yukki, no fair.
Huh?
What's wrong?
It's empty.
Huh? That's odd.
I thought there was still a lot left.
Why don't you help out again next year?
You might get some next time.
Good work, guys.
Akira-chan, come again next year.
Good work.
I smell a perfect crime.
A perfect... what?
I'm too tired to even respond to that,
so go be stupid somewhere else.
Just hear me out, gentlemen.
The candy didn't just disappear.
It was stolen!
There isn't a single fingerprint at the scene of the crime.
There's no record of you checking for fingerprints, either.
Naturally, no one saw the culprit wipe off his prints.
Which means...
He must have been wearing gloves!
We're all wearing gloves.
Wh-What?
What are you trying to do?
What I'm trying to say
is that Choco-Banana's our prime suspect.
In his Santa bag, that white sack,
he's got the madness and greed known as the hunger for candy!
Also, it's our candy in there!
Where are you going?
Let go!
Choco-Banana, show yourself!
You're the one who's greedy here.
What's wrong? Is everything all right?
Sorry, he's just tired.
Let go!
You've seen how he acts.
It's gotta be him!
No, Chizuru-kun!
You can't accuse him based on that!
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
The reindeer?
This smells like a perfect crime.
Hey, not you too.
We're not the only ones who wouldn't leave fingerprints.
I told you. It was Choco-Banana.
There's someone else.
No. No way.
It couldn't have been the reindeer.
The candy...
Excuse me.
Stop it!
J-Just take this off.
What are you doing with all of this?
Hand
Potato
Chips
Hand
Hand
Some of our products are in there too.
He ran away!
After him! Hurry!
Chizuru.
M-Me?!
Where're my caramels?
Outta the way!
Watch out!
Are you all right?
That was a bit of a surprise, wasn't it?
Here.
A present from Santa for being a good little boy.
Have a merry, merry Christmas.
Thanks, Santa.
You're very welcome.
Bye bye!
Choco-Banana...
Who are you?
I'm Santa Claus.
This day has really been exhausting.
Why did I have to work so hard on Christmas Eve?
Because you knocked over that tree.
No, in the first place, it was...
It was because you suggested we rent more DVDs.
No matter how far you go back, it always comes back to Chizuru.
Come on.
You guys wanted to watch more, too.
What should we do about the DVDs?
Want to call it a night?
Of course not.
This is our time now!
Our DVD Christmas!
But I don't see the DVDs in question anywhere.
Kanamecchi, where are they?
How would I know?
I don't know.
I dunno.
Me either.
I might have left them at the mall.
What?!
Crap. This is so awful that I can't even muster up the strength to yell at you.
What is this?
I hear jingle bells ringing in my head.
Yuuki-kun, that's called a headache.
Who could that be at this hour?
Maybe it's Santa.
Shun-chan, we graduated from believing in Santa long ago.
Here.
Our DVDs!
Akira found them.
You left them in the event area.
You should be grateful.
Thank you, but how did you know they were ours?
Because they were in the picture.
Santa!
I thought you just said you had graduated from that.
Are you sure?
Since you came all the way here, you should enjoy yourselves.
Are you really sure?
It looks like you were having fun.
It's fine. It's fine.
We've been running around all over the place,
so we're just getting started.
Do you drink coffee, Sensei?
Yes, please.
I'll have a hot cocoa!
I didn't ask you!
I hope we can actually do something fun next Christmas.
Maybe we'll splurge a bit.
By splurge, I bet you just mean we'll each get a single parfait.
You underestimate me. We'll get two each.
That's hardly different.
They're so carefree.
Won't they be in the middle of their entrance exams at this time next year?
Yeah, but you can't picture that until you actually go through it.
Is that how it is?
I thought growing older would turn me into an adult.
I thought I'd get a job, get married,
and somehow become an adult version of myself.
Cocoa
But nothing like that happened.
Are you jealous of them?
Maybe.
I guess we'll have to be high schoolers again.
You're right.
I've still never truly felt that I've become an adult.
But I know I'm no longer a child.
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "In The Steam."
In The Steam