After returning from our long break in May,
we have a mock entrance exam.
However, spring still holds our class
in its drowsy grasp, without any sense of anxiety.
This sucks.
Why do we have to take a mock exam?
It's not worth losing precious vacation days.
I know, right?
This is like having to work on a day off.
On a mock exam, don't we have to write down the school we want to attend?
I still don't know what I want to do yet,
so I never know what to write.
Maybe I'll put down the University of Tokyo as my number one choice,
even though I'll probably get an F.
No, an F would be too good for you.
Chizuru, you're a Z.
I don't care.
Anyway, do you guys want to go get ramen after school?
A new place opened in front of the station.
Just for today, they're selling ramen for 100 yen a bowl.
Really? Thick broth or thin broth?
Full-flavored pork-bone broth ramen bursting with grease!
Oh, sorry.
I have to go to a club meeting today.
The Tea Club meets today?
Shun-chan, I'll be so lonely without you.
So lonely!
Is tea club fun?
Yes, it sure is.
Once a week, our tea instructor comes by,
and we drink tea and eat delicious traditional sweets.
You eat traditional sweets, too?
That sounds great.
You get to have snack time in the middle of your club meeting!
The Tea Club sure sounds fun.
Maybe I should give it a try...
Chizuru-kun, why don't you come with me today?
You can come just to try it out.
What? Really?
Yes, of course.
Yuuki-kun, if you'd like, you can come, too.
Really? Me, too?
Yes. I'll go tell Yuuta-kun about it.
Hooray.
Chizuru, what about the ramen?
Nah, s'okay. We can go there afterwards.
What's with the fake Kansai accent?
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
Yuuta-kun, Kaname-kun.
Today, I'm...
Universipedia
Comprehensive guide
to the most famous
universities
Shun, what's wrong?
Oh, um...
I was talking to Chizuru-kun and Yuuki-kun about them coming to the tea club with me today...
Well, it should be okay.
We always seem to have more sweets than we need.
They're just going for the sweets, aren't they?
Kaname, do you want to come, too?
Huh? No.
I need to study for tomorrow's mock exam.
Don't be like that.
Universipedia
Comprehensive guide
to the most famous
universities
Stuff like this is good for people like you.
It'll help lower your daily stress.
Whose younger brother do you think stresses me out?
Strawberry
Marshmallows
They've been thinking about it...
It's time for us to decide what we want to do with our lives.
It's not like before.
Let's go outside and play tag!
Yeah, let's go!
You're "it"!
I wonder if kisses are fluffy like marshmallows.
How embarrassing!
How long have you been watching?
Not long.
Since you started looking for a nearby stuffed animal.
You saw the whole thing!
What were you doing, anyway?
I was practicing.
I don't want to mess up my life's one and only first kiss.
I see.
What do you do with your hands when you kiss?
Do you keep them at your sides?
What? That would ruin the mood.
Isn't the man supposed to hold the other person's hands?
Gently and softly.
Like this?
But Kaname-kun, if you don't firmly grab on to the person's shoulders,
won't she run away from you?
What about your eyes?
Who's supposed to close them?
But Kaname-kun, if you close your eyes,
won't she escape while she has the chance?
You can't let your guard down even for an instant.
Shut up, already!
Oh, your breath!
Can you breathe while you kiss?
I can't even hold my breath for ten seconds.
Your breath, huh?
I guess your mouths are stuck together.
If you get caught up in the moment, would you suffocate to death?
Wouldn't it be wonderful to leave this world...
while embracing the one you love?
Wouldn't it?
That's so dramatic!
No way!
Love's meant to be shared while you're alive!
What are you doing?
Yuuta-kun!
Nothing!
Universipedia
Comprehensive guide
to the most famous
universities
Universipedia
Comprehensive guide
to the most famous
universities
Universipedia
Comprehensive guide
to the most famous
universities
Here.
Universipedia
Comprehensive guide
to the most famous
universities
Universipedia
Comprehensive guide
to the most famous
universities
You seemed interested in it, so you can borrow it.
It's Kaname's, though.
Well, see you later.
Okay, get to your seats.
Chizuru-kun. Yuuki-kun.
I have to go get ready, so I'll go on ahead.
Okay. We'll catch up later.
Oh, Matsuoka-kun.
Yes?
Did you have a question about something?
What?
Well, if you don't, that's fine.
Um...
Azuma-sensei, when did you decide to become a teacher?
Probably... when I started university.
When I was deciding my major,
I naturally started thinking about
what sort of job I'd like to have.
So you'd already decided what you wanted to do
by the time you were our age.
Well, I guess so.
I see.
Thank you. Excuse me.
There!
Shun-chan?
Shun-chan!
Masaki-chan!
Y-You're going to your club now?
Yes.
I see.
B-Boys don't usually join the Tea Club.
Shun-chan, why did you join the Tea Club?
I don't really have a reason.
When I passed by their room while we were checking out all of the clubs,
the tea smelled really nice.
Yuuta-kun said he would join too, so...
I see. I just thought it was nice.
See you later.
Have fun at your club.
Okay.
I really don't think about anything.
Shun-chan.
Let's get started.
Oh, right.
Sorry.
I'll start by teaching you the basics of sitting.
What? Who cares about that?
Where are the sweets?
I'm hungry.
No, Chizuru-kun!
Graceful movements are an important element of the tea ceremony.
Okay, first, straighten your spine like you're sticking out your navel.
I told you that I don't care.
It's too stiff.
A beautiful posture makes you look cooler, you know.
Come on, Shun-chan, if good
posture was all it took to be a man,
no one would have to...
What?
Shun-chan, what did you say about navels?
It's cool for your navel to jump out?
No, you have to stick it out.
Forward, forward, forward, forward...
If it jumped out, it'd be an outie.
Like this, Shun-chan?
It's quite loud in here. Are these your friends?
Tsunashi-sensei.
They're all here to experience the club today.
I see. How wonderful.
Young people aren't often interested.
This is Tsunashi-sensei, the man who teaches us how to perform a tea ceremony.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Tsunashi.
Is there something on my head?
No, nothing.
There's nothing on your head... at all.
Matsuoka-kun, I'll leave them to you.
Yes.
Hey, you're not little kids anymore.
Don't make such a fuss over what's on a person's head.
I'm not laughing.
But Yuutan, a bald person suddenly entering your day...
would be enough to shock anyone.
You idiot.
I was so surprised.
I thought a giant white dango had walked in.
Hey Yuuki-kun, he'll hear you!
I see.
It seems that you're all quite interested in my head.
"Respect and tranquility."
Hairless and receding?
It's an expression coined by Rikyu to express...
the spirit of the tea ceremony.
"Approach tea with respect for others...
and with a harmonious, pure, and tranquil heart."
In others words, you must...
treasure the relaxation provided by an unmoved heart,
no matter what happens, even if my head is bald.
This is what it means.
That's right.
No matter what kind of hairstyle appears before you,
your heart must never move.
This is delicious!
These sweets are delicious!
And they look so nice!
Do you guys always eat stuff like this?
This is the best!
I'm glad you like it.
A tea ceremony with delicious tea and traditional sweets.
Looks like I know what I wanna do in life.
You do?
I'll follow the path of tea.
Note: Ochanomizu University = "Tea-water University"
I'll write Ochanomizu University as my first choice school...
on tomorrow's mock exam.
They don't study tea there.
And it's a girls' school.
Don't bother.
Tea isn't something you can do, Chizuru.
You don't know that yet.
Right, Tsunashi-sensei?
Well, I'm very happy to meet a young person who feels that way.
See?
In that case, while you're here today,
why don't you learn about the ceremony in more detail?
Really?
All right!
Learning about this ceremony will turn me,
a lowly third year in high school, into more of an adult!
You And Me.
This is nice.
Watching this sort of thing always calms me.
Yeah.
All of your stress will be washed away.
I don't think I can wash all of it away with this meager amount of tea, though.
Chizuru, are you watching this?
He's going out of his way for you...
You idiot!
Don't poke my feet!
Huh?
I can't feel anything.
It must have fallen asleep.
Try some thick tea.
Huh? Just me?
You're meant to pass the thick tea around and share it with everyone.
It's so bitter!
Bitter! Why is it so freaking bitter?!
So bitter!
How is your bowl?
Huh?
How is my what?
He's asking you about the strength of the tea.
In the Japanese tea ceremony, each drink
is called a "bowl" instead of a cup.
When he asks you,
you're supposed to tell him "It's fine."
Yeah, it's definitely fine!
Completely fine!
Do you call this a "bowl" because you put a bowl of poison in it?
Is that why it's so lethally bitter?
Matsuoka-kun,
why don't you get everyone to look at the implements?
What? What are we looking at?
Well, after you drink tea,
you're supposed to pick up the bowl you used and look at it.
But...
Most bowls used for thick tea are expensive,
so make sure you don't damage or break it.
Especially you, Chizuru-san.
Hey, if you tell me not to break something,
I'm bound to break it.
You should give up on the path of tea
and follow the path of comedy instead.
I don't get it.
Why is this thing so expensive?
I wouldn't give this a second thought even if someone served me boiled potatoes in this.
I know, right? If people pay money for this,
I could've made a fortune in a single summer as a grade schooler.
Don't treat this like your summer art projects.
And doesn't it look like a reject?
Its shape is all distorted, see?
I bet they try to trick you by saying that this distortion enhances the "flavor."
You're the ones who are distorted.
I wonder how much it is. It's expensive, right?
Note: Noguchi Hideyo is on the 1,000 yen bill. Fukuzawa Yuukichi is on the 10,000 yen bill.
Three Noguchi Hideyos?
Three Fukuzawa Yuukichis.
You idiot! Don't let me hold something so expensive!
What are you doing?!
I'm done.
I can't do this tea stuff.
Who was it? Who recommended the path of tea to me?
You did.
How unfortunate.
However, should you ever feel the calling again,
please try pursuing the path of tea.
You can obtain a teaching license through study at any age.
What? Really?
Tsunashi-sensei, when did you decide to become a tea instructor?
When was it?
My family has been teaching the tea ceremony for generations,
so I have studied tea since I was very young.
I never thought about making this my future career,
and I certainly never thought I'd become a tea instructor.
What?
Really? Then why did you follow the path of tea?
Well...
Probably because I was much better at it than language or math.
What? That's it?
Surprisingly, yes.
That means when you were our age...
I hadn't really thought about it.
Only a few people can imagine their future
in their third year of high school.
Tsunashi-sensei, you were a lot like Chizuru.
You both started tea on a whim.
Oh? Does that mean what I think it means?
Doesn't that mean I might become a tea instructor?
No, you're not cut from the same cloth.
What did you say?
When I grow up, I'll be a proper adult like Tsunashi-sensei!
Right?
Is that the last bell?
Is it that late already?
Let's go, Yukki!
They might run out of ramen!
Chizuru-kun...
The only thing that's changed since I became an adult...
is that unlike when I was younger,
my legs don't fall asleep when I sit anymore.
Where did everyone go?
They left.
They said they were off to eat ramen.
Kaname said that he wanted to study for the mock exam.
I see.
Shun.
Yes?
Do you want me to make you some tea?
What?
You spent all of your time teaching everyone today,
so you didn't get to drink any of it.
How is your bowl?
Yuuta-kun, have you already decided which university you want to go to?
Oh, it's just that you were looking at a college reference book today, so...
No, I don't know yet.
I was just looking to see what's out there.
I wonder why we have to write what school we want to attend on a mock exam.
I don't know what to do about it.
You're right.
But I...
Unlike you, I still haven't even researched colleges yet.
Even though everyone around us is acting like there isn't a test,
Kaname-kun's studying for tomorrow.
It's amazing.
I haven't even thought about what I want to do,
so I was surprised to see what the two of you were doing.
Not so much surprised, but... well...
Shun.
Your navel.
How is your bowl?
It is fine.
haru no kaze ni
kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished
into the spring breeze
Huh?
boku ga hitori de
kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it
come true by myself
What's wrong?
We've been waiting.
We decided to study for tomorrow's test at Kanamecchi's.
Sheesh.
What about your ramen?
nee
Hey
We can pick up some instant ramen on the way home.
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
You can make it, Kaname.
I have to do it?
All you have to do is pour hot water on it.
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
Let's go!
How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto
mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having
difficult times
We still can't imagine...
kimi he to todoku
ki ga suru kara
I believe this
will reach you
our futures or foresee what they hold,
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going?
yet we'll all change slowly but surely.
motto issho ni
I hope we can
Shun-chan, let's go!
waraitakute
katariaitakute
laugh and talk
together again
In this way, we've matured a little.
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku
ki ga suru kara
I believe this
will reach you
Coming!
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Navel and Dignity