What?
Kanamecchi, your parents are leaving today
to go on vacation overseas, and they'll be gone four days and three nights?
Yeah.
They managed to get some time off,
so they're going with Hisako's parents.
Oh, sounds wonderful!
I see.
I guess that means you'll be home alone, Kaname.
You won't be able to see your beloved mom.
Hey, are you going to be okay being so far away from her for three whole days?
I'll be perfectly fine!
What sort of person are you guys trying to make me out to be, anyway?
If the Tsukahara mother and son can last three whole days apart,
we'd better submit it to the Guinness Book of World Records.
I know, right?
But will you really be okay?
What about meals?
I'll be eating next door while my mom's gone.
Hisako's sister said that she'd make dinner for me.
Shizuna-oneechan, you mean?
Yeah.
I don't know if she's suddenly taken an interest in cooking,
but she's been practicing a lot.
Going over there just to eat is such a pain in the ass.
But I guess it's better than cooking for myself,
so I might as well.
I see.
What a pain.
But Kaname-kun, you look kinda happy about it.
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
I cut too much off.
No way! He's here already?
You're here early.
Were you asleep or something?
Your hair's a mess.
What?
Um, something like that.
Where's Shizu-nee?
Oh, she's getting everything ready.
Welcome, Kaname-kun.
Hi, Shizu-nee.
I thought I was only here to eat.
Of course not.
Those who don't work don't get to eat.
You'll be helping me again tomorrow.
And the day after, you'll go shopping.
I want you to go to the supermarket with Hisako-chan.
Huh?
What?
That's too much work.
There's going to be a big sale on eggs tomorrow,
but they're limited to one carton per customer.
That's why I want both of you to go.
Shizu-nee, your sleeves will get wet.
Huh? Oh.
Jeez... Here.
It's okay. I can do it.
Just let me.
Delicious.
The three of us haven't eaten together in a while.
We used to go to each other's houses all the time.
Kaname-kun, aren't you going to come over
to show me your perfect test scores anymore?
No.
That's right, Onee-chan.
It's pretty hard to get a perfect score on tests in high school.
I wouldn't come even if I did!
Mind if I have some more?
Go ahead.
My curry must be a big hit!
No, I'm just so hungry that anything tastes good.
You're always so mean.
My sister's expanding her repertoire like crazy right now.
What's she going to do when it's bigger?
Meet prospective suitors?
Well, I guess no one would marry you if you couldn't cook.
Sounds like a good idea.
You should learn to make meat and potatoes next...
What?
Kaname-kun, your mother didn't tell you?
Tell me what?
I'm getting married.
To a co-worker of mine.
Oh? That's odd.
I went over to tell your mother just the other day.
Kaname-kun?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
That's great. Congratulations.
Thanks.
You're getting married, huh? I had no idea.
I see.
Is he reading?
No, he can't be.
He hasn't turned the page in ages.
Kaname-kun has seemed down all morning.
I wonder what's wrong...
Maybe Captain Comeback's cutting back on his hours?
We are in a recession.
That's not it, kids.
This is a case of a rabbit dying from loneliness.
Huh? Why is he lonely?
Oh, you don't think...
That's right! He's trying to be strong,
but it's really hard for him...
to not see his mom!
Can't you see it?
Can't you see his eyes, red with tears
like a little bunny's every night?
The only time I've seen Kaname's eyes red is when they're red with rage.
I wonder if there's anything we can do.
I know. I'll bring back Kaname's mom.
In four days and three nights.
You just want to go on an overseas vacation.
I have a good idea.
Kaname-kun's late.
He was already here by this time yesterday.
Yeah.
Maybe Kaname's not planning on coming over to eat today.
You're late. Dinner's already...
Good evening!
My, my. What are all of you doing here?
It's good to see you again!
Because Kanamecchi's broken-hearted from not seeing his mother,
we've come over today to cheer him up with a fun dinner party!
That sounds like fun. Come on in.
All right! Excuse the intrusion.
My mother made this stew, if you'd like it.
This is our sautéed and simmered burdock.
This is yesterday's leftover meat and potatoes.
Thank you.
You're heartbroken because you can't see your mom?
Of course not.
I told them that, but they insisted on eating with us,
so I had to bring them over.
You seem relieved, though.
What?
Nothing.
Sorry for bringing all these people, Shizu-nee.
It's okay.
They brought us food,
and it's always more fun to eat with lots of people.
Really? That's good, then.
Ouch! These onions hurt so much!
You can do it.
Imagine that ginger-fried pork right before your eyes.
But I can't see!
I can't see it through my tears!
What is this?
This just seems like a last ditch attempt to avoid being eaten.
You're the ones who said you'd do your part of the cooking, right?
Shut up and cut your onions.
But this is really tough!
That's right.
It's not just us. The entire USA would be in tears over this.
Switch with us! Kanamecchi, you cut some next!
Kaname, you won't cry.
Your heart isn't pure enough.
Don't give me that.
How rude.
Ow!
No, no, I can't do this. I can't keep my eyes open.
Then just cut it with your eyes closed!
I'll cut my hand off!
You don't have a choice.
The word "shouga-yaki" originates from the phrase "shou ga nai".
Note: "shougayaki" = ginger-fried foods. "shou ga nai" = can't help it.
It does not!
Oh?
Milk
Coffee -
Kaname-kun.
Do you think we could use some of the soy sauce from your house?
We don't have much left.
Yeah, sure. I'll go get it.
Jeez, I can't believe that slave driver.
Soy sauce, soy sauce...
I can't cut onions anymore!
Miss, please switch with me!
Okay, okay.
Good try.
I didn't ask how much soy sauce she needed.
Maybe I should take the big one.
Soy sauce, soy sauce...
Your mother didn't tell you?
I'm getting married to a co-worker of mine.
Married?
Why do you have to get married?
You And Me.
See you later.
Thanks for having us.
Thanks for the food.
That was amazing.
They were as loud as grade schoolers having lunch.
Well, tomorrow, the three of us can have a nice, quiet—
Hisako.
I'll pass on dinner tomorrow.
What?
It's too much work to come over here and help with things.
"Too much work"?
Tell Shizu-nee for me.
See you later.
Wait, Kaname!
Has everyone left?
Yeah.
I see.
Don't forget to buy two cartons of eggs with Kaname tomorrow.
Oh, about that. Kaname just said...
What should I make?
We'll have lots of eggs,
so I was thinking either omelet rice or oyakodon.
You're not going to cut your bangs?
Huh?
You've been keeping them long for a while.
I look young if I cut my bangs.
Young? You're only 25.
I'm already 25.
So, should we have omelet rice or oyakodon tomorrow?
I'll ask Kaname!
It's me. Do you have a minute?
What do you want?
Don't give me that.
Your door wasn't locked.
Oh.
Oh?
Well?
I wanted to talk to you about dinner tomorrow.
Are you sure you won't come eat?
I told you; I'll pass.
But my sister asked us to buy two cartons of eggs at the supermarket because they're on sale tomorrow.
She's going to make either omelet rice or oyakodon with them.
We wouldn't have to help much with those.
Which do you prefer, Kaname?
Either's fine.
I haven't had omelet rice recently.
Why don't you make that, then?
Don't be like that. Actually think about it—
Like I said, either's—
Ow, that hurt!
What was that for?
Because you're answering like you don't even care!
If her marriage bothers you this much,
you should've told her how you feel already!
What? What are you—
It's obvious!
I've known that you like my sister for ages!
You should just tell her.
Maybe nothing will come of it, but at least...
It's fine.
It's not like that, anyway.
I never thought about telling her or dating her.
It's more like I admire her, so...
But...
Kaname, you love her.
Even if you just admire her, you also love her.
Hey, wait. Why are you crying?
Hold on.
Here, have a tissue.
Tell her, you idiot!
What's her problem?
What's that supposed to mean?
I have too much on my mind.
I don't feel like going to the supermarket to buy eggs.
Kaname-kun, good timing.
I was just on my way over.
I thought we could go to the supermarket together.
Hisako-chan has a quiz tomorrow, so she doesn't have time to go.
She told me to go instead.
That meddler...
Kaname-kun?
Is something wrong?
Oh, not at all.
Let's go, then.
Hanamura
Supermarket
All right, two cartons of eggs.
Milk
Are you really going to use all those?
You can never have too many eggs.
You can use them to make all sorts of dishes.
Now that I've expanded my repertoire, just leave it to me.
Oh, sorry.
Not at all. Sorry.
Why are you spacing out like that?
I was wondering what we were having for dinner.
That's all you ever think about.
Kaname-kun!
Kaname-kun, over here!
You don't need to shout. What?
Don't give me that.
When I turned around, you were gone.
Here, this is for you.
Hey...
We can't just eat that.
What if they pressure us into buying it?
You worry too much.
It's only a sample, so don't get so worked up. Just eat it.
I had already decided to buy it before I started to eat it.
You're the one who's getting worked up.
Would you like another one?
Yes, please.
How much are you going to eat?
You two are quite the couple.
I would've bought some even if you hadn't said that.
Why, thank you.
We bought so much.
Sorry. I always end up getting more
when there's a guy to help me carry.
If you knew it was gonna be heavy,
I wish you'd been faster deciding which flavor of taiyaki you wanted.
Sorry, sorry.
Let's take a break, then.
Hey, don't blame me if you spoil your appetite.
It's okay.
Here.
Okay, I'm next!
Ready, set, go!
I win!
Darn it!
Shizu-nee, look!
I found some awesome grass!
No matter who I play grass sumo with, it never loses!
That's amazing, Kaname-kun.
Ready, set, go!
I lost again.
Kaname-kun, you're so good at this.
Shizu-nee, you're just too weak.
You should choose some stronger grass.
I'm trying.
Um, about your... wedding.
What?
Uh, well...
What's he like? Is he good looking?
Oh, I don't know if I'd say that.
All my friends say he kinda looks like "The Bear in the Forest".
What? That's harsh.
But he's nice.
Not just to me, but to everyone.
What about the ceremony?
When is it?
Oh, and you'll have to find somewhere to live.
Do you think, you know, you'll end up pretty far from here?
I guess you'll be okay with cooking.
You've been expanding your repertoire recently.
It's amazing.
The most I can do is wash rice...
That's because you're so clumsy.
Clumsy? I know I'm not good at cooking, but...
No, you're clumsy.
Not just at cooking, but everything.
You're not better than anyone else.
You study hard when no one's looking,
and even though you're clumsy,
if anyone asks you for help,
you always try to do more than you're capable of.
But you try not to show that side of yourself to anyone.
I know, because we've been together since you were little.
Well, anyway, that's what's good about you.
You try so hard without expecting praise—
I got praise.
You praised me, Shizu-nee.
You'd call me amazing, and you'd smile.
I was really happy when you smiled for me.
When I was little, I would do anything to get her attention.
Perfect test scores, back hip circles, report cards,
the first time I became Class President...
I showed her anything I could brag about.
Because she was always so close.
She always smiled for me.
I never thought about confessing to her.
I never thought about dating her.
But still, I...
They're playing grass sumo.
So weird.
Playing kids' games even though they're adults.
They're just big kids! Big kids!
We should get going.
Kaname-kun, you can wash the rice.
Sure.
Kaname-kun.
Do you want omelet rice or oyakodon?
Oyakodon.
Did you tell her yesterday?
Tell her what?
Did you tell my sister that you like her?
No.
What?!
C-Come on!
Why do you think I set that up—
I told you; it's fine.
It's fine.
Thanks for everything.
Maybe I'll let my bangs grow out.
Who, you?
No way.
You'll totally give up and cut them before they've grown.
That's not true.
I'll definitely do it this time.
Oh, right.
My sister made lunch for me today.
Complete with a whole load of fried eggs.
Seriously?
She said that she expanded her repertoire,
and all she's making is fried eggs?
Stripped Bare
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "Navel and Dignity."
Navel and Dignity