All right. Let's have lunch!
Chizuru-kun, you seem happy.
Of course I am.
Now that the proficiency test is over, I'm officially free!
Yay! It's over!
Huh? Where's Yukki?
There he is.
Yukki, hurry u—
Chizuru, your blazer's getting in your rice bowl.
Huh? No way!
Just kidding.
Huh? Come on. I got the curry udon today...
Don't joke around like that.
Hey, you'd better not get any curry on me, you monkey.
I can't promise that.
You must be doing well if you're eating school lunches again.
Did you collect 30 sticker points yet?
No, not yet.
I've already exchanged my stickers for a plate.
I see.
How many points do you have now?
Seventeen points.
That number hasn't changed in a while.
I'm stuck in a rut.
I'm sick of sticker duty!
No more! No more, I say!
We abolished our sticker duty rotation.
There you go again with that "Sticker duty."
You've mentioned it before, but what is it exactly?
Well, it's...
Asaba?
You're Asaba, right? From Class 4?
This is great. You're really tall.
It'd be better if you had shorter hair, though.
Excuse me...
Let's take a look at your muscles.
Oh, sorry. I guess you don't know who I am.
I'm Yanagi from Class 7. Nice to meet you.
My hands are occupied right now.
Didn't you just use your hand to brush him off a second ago?
Asaba, do you have any interest in basketball?
asa no sakamichi kudaru sono saki ni
While going down the slope in the morning
mujaki ni warau kimi wo mitsuketa
I found you, laughing innocently
"ohayou" tte hitokoto ga kyou mo ienakute
Today, yet again, I'm unable to greet you with "good morning"
doushite kimi ni wa futsuu no boku ja irarenai'n darou
I wonder why I'm unable to be myself in front of you
zutto kimi ga kimi dake ga afureteru yo
My head is always filled with thoughts of you and only you
mou kono kimochi osaekirenai yo
I can no longer stop these feelings
iitai'n dakedo ienai'n da yo
I want to tell you about it, but can't
kimi ga mabushisugite
You are brighter than the sun
motto kimi no sugusoba de waraeru you ni
I wish I could laugh beside you for a while longer
kokoro no naka de sou negatteru yo
from the bottom of my heart
itsu no hi ka kimi dake ni kono omoi ga todoku to ii na
I hope my feelings will be able to reach you one day
Free Plate
Point
My brother, whose sole interest is manga,
has taken a surprising interest in the
curly-haired Cinderella of the cafeteria.
Free Plate
Point
Since then, his "same old, same old" days have become a bit more colorful.
Free Plate
Point
What? The basketball team tried to recruit you?
That's amazing. They scouted you?
They said that they're not as strong since the third years left.
Of course, I turned him down on the spot.
But why you?
Yuuki's played a game with the Basketball Club before.
Maybe that's why.
When did you play, Yukki?
When he was trying to find a club last spring.
Yuuki-kun was pretty amazing at it!
You jerk! When will you find time to hang out with me if you join a demanding club like the Basketball Club?
Like I said, I turned him down.
You should just join.
You can find all the sweat, hard work, and high fives you've been missing
from your youth at the Basketball Club.
Asaba Yuuki on the basketball team...
Sweat and hard work...
and high fives...
This shrimp is delicious.
I can't do it. I can't even picture it.
I think I did, just a little.
It was really blurry, though.
That's amazing, Yuuta-kun!
I couldn't see anything.
I know. Pretty serious, right? So...
No, no!
I won't let you join the club!
Why does he need your permission?
Thanks for the food.
Why didn't they try to scout me, anyway?
Dish
Return
I wonder why...
Hey, wait a sec.
Come here a sec.
We'll go on ahead.
What is it?
You can have my stickers.
I started collecting them to get a second plate,
but I don't think I can get enough in time.
There, got it.
That's all you got?
That's hardly worth it.
It's worth plenty.
For a poor student like you, this is a good deal!
Here's your sticker.
Did you see the new design?
The second plate's pretty cute, too.
I'm so hungry.
Why don't you get that today?
What? You don't want it?
No, I do...
Kayo, we've got some more hungry students.
Okay.
Well, anyway, these are yours.
Huh. So she gave you her stickers.
Yeah.
That's the second time.
Asaba.
Have you thought about joining us?
Didn't I tell you that I'm not interested?
You're no fun!
Tada!
If you join our club,
maybe I'll give you these stickers. Or something.
Your invitation is turning into a business deal.
If all it takes are some measly stickers, it's not a big deal to me.
For you, maybe.
I'm surprised that you know Yuuki is collecting stickers.
You can get this kind of info in an instant if you just ask the girls.
For the second giveaway campaign,
if you collect 30 stickers, you'll receive an entire Anpanda plate.
Don't you want some...
Hey!
Wait!
Just come watch us play!
What's your problem?
Get away from my Yukki.
Cafeteria - Store
Oh, it's just you.
Were you sleeping?
Just thinking.
If you'd have arrived a little earlier,
you could've helped me wipe down the tables again.
Did you cut your finger again?
Not this time.
Oh.
Sorry, did you come here to buy something?
No.
Um, I came to get some stickers.
Stickers?
Don't start thinking that other people will always be around to help you.
But you gave me some the other day.
That was then.
You shouldn't rely on me for all of your stickers.
I'm quitting this job soon.
What?
I'm quitting at the end of the week.
I'm going to work in a salon again.
"Again"?
It might surprise you, but I used to
work in a salon before ending up here.
I'm not bad at styling hair and doing makeup.
Why are you making that face?
No reason.
I'll have to start living on my own, so it'll be tough.
I'll have to pack and stuff.
The end of the week.
You don't want to go?
No, that's not it.
I think it'd be just fine if you kept working in the cafeteria.
It doesn't seem like a salon would be as much fun.
I told you, that's not it.
But you already quit once.
Do you really want to work there again that badly?
What? Are you calling me selfish?
No, that's not what I—
What, then?
Excuse me.
Is the shop closed for the day?
Oh, you're fine. Sorry, sorry.
You And Me.
Oh, you got a 74 in English?
Yes!
That's pretty good for you, Shun.
English isn't your strongest subject.
It's because everyone helped me study.
Chizuru, how did you do?
Dunno if I should show you.
The divine radiance of my grade might blind your mortal eyes.
That bad?
Just show us.
Chizuru-kun.
No, no! You'll laugh!
Those two never laugh.
I'm sorry we asked you to show us.
Well, they do say, "Live fast; die young," don't they?
What? Am I that screwed?
Come on! I bet you're one to talk, Yukki...
Second
Year
English
Answer
Sheet
Year
Class
Name
Asaba
Yuuki
Huh, 81?! Isn't that higher than normal?
You studied harder than usual this time around. Right, Yuuki?
Traitor!
Who cares, you monkey?
I'm sure you made someone happy
by dragging down the average with your failing grade.
Even morons like you can do the world some good—
Monkey...!
Well, you suck at teaching, Kanamecchi!
What did you say?!
You should wait until you evolve from
a monkey into a human being before you say that!
It went outside!
Chizuru, you should have caught it.
There's no way I could catch such a painful truth!
Someone picked it up.
You're kidding.
Look, it's the girl from the cafeteria.
I can't let the Cafeteria Cinderella see that.
Let's go, Shun-chan.
What? Me, too?
Here, Tachibana Chizuru-kun.
Second Year
Se
c
ond
Semes
ter Quiz
English Answer Sheet
Year
Class
Name
Tachibana Chizuru
Her impression of me is ruined.
Thank you.
You should try a little harder.
Aren't you worried about your entrance exams?
Nah. In this day and age,
it's better to get work experience than attend college.
Just like you're doing.
Like me?
Don't you have a catering license?
No, I don't have anything like that.
What? You don't?
After I graduated from high school, I studied hair and makeup.
No wonder your hair's so beautiful.
Hey.
Ouch.
Don't touch a lady's hair without her permission, kid.
Hey.
We're leaving.
Okay.
You guys are such good friends.
You eat lunch together and walk home together, too.
One of you didn't come to the cafeteria today.
Yeah, Yukki wanted to eat in the classroom.
I see.
We'll all come to the cafeteria again.
Okay.
Oh, I...
Oh, well.
Anpanda Plate
Present
I'm hungry.
Cafeteria - Store
You can't fight on an empty stomach.
Dish
Return
Fight what? Do you have to retake your test?
Hey.
Yes?
I get the feeling that one of you...
hasn't come to the cafeteria for a few days now.
Oh, Yuuki's eating bread in the classroom again.
I see.
What do you mean by "I see"? Hurry up and get serving!
Ow!
Can't you at least work hard on your last day?
I always work hard.
Go say goodbye to the teachers before you leave.
Okay, okay.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
Not at all.
Um...
She's quitting?
Oh, Kayo?
Yes, today's her last day.
I see.
Don't worry. I'll take extra good care of you to make up for her leaving.
Oh.
You too, Miss.
Um, I'm not a girl.
Oh, my. Really? I'm so sorry.
Hey.
Um, I...
Four more points.
Yuuki-kun.
Can I eat here, too?
Sure, but why aren't you eating in the cafeteria?
I feel like eating bread today.
I'll just pull up a chair.
It's nice when it's only the two of us once in a while.
You don't have to worry about me.
You could've eaten in the cafeteria.
If Kaname and Chizuru fight, who's going to stop them?
I know, but I thought you might be lonely by yourself.
I'm fine.
But...
When I thought about you eating all by yourself, I got all sad.
My mom will be lonely, eating by herself.
The end of the week.
That doesn't bother me, so I wouldn't know.
Oh, I see.
But...
People who don't like it must really hate it.
Yuuki-kun?
You almost have all of the stickers you need.
What? You're going to join us?
I didn't say that.
I just said that I wanted your stickers.
Stickers, huh?
You really got my hopes up.
I didn't expect you to come talk to me.
Let's play a quick game.
If you can get past my defense and get a basket,
I'll give you the stickers.
But if you lose the ball to me or miss your shot,
you have to join the club.
I'm in a rush, so let's hurry this up.
You're no fun.
Can't you just think for a second about joining the club?
Is collecting stickers even fun?
I'm sure basketball's more...
Huh?
I'm in a hurry. Can I have my stickers?
Cafeteria - Store
What are you doing?
I'm the one asking the questions here.
Dish
Return
What's this?
MEAL TICKETS
You can have it.
This is the plate from the convenience store!
You don't want it?
It's a gift.
Because you were angry.
I wasn't angry. I was just venting a little.
Is it really okay for me to have this?
Also...
I don't think it's bad for you...
to leave your mom and live on your own.
Dish
Return
It's turning red!
You're a young guy. You can run faster than that!
Come on!
My mom usually talks a lot.
The first time I moved out,
she was quiet all the way to the station.
She was absolutely silent while we waited at crossings.
She'd speak a little, but you know...
I figured that she was choosing her words carefully.
The more you get that feeling,
the worse it gets.
When I quit the salon,
I thought my mom would scold me.
Tell me not to be such a baby.
But she told me to come home.
When things got tough, I ran back to my mom.
But now, I'm running out to chase after what I want,
and I'm leaving my mom on her own again.
I think...
your mother will probably just go home and watch TV like she always does.
You're the only one concerned about it.
Really?
You're right.
It's not a bad thing to have something you want to do.
I don't really have anything.
What are you babbling about?
You have your whole life ahead of you.
Lots of decisions and choices...
Lots of meetings and partings.
I'm jealous.
It's green.
I'm going this way.
Oh, are you?
Well, bye bye.
Please use that plate.
Even if it's only once in a while.
Sure, I will.
Thanks.
Liar.
Jeez, what are you doing?
Just take what you need for now.
I know.
You'll come back for New Year's and Bon, won't you?
Yeah.
Goodness, don't go to work with your hair looking like that, okay?
I know.
That kid.
Kaname, is Yuuki in there?
Yuuki?
Isn't he drooling over some magazine like always?
Man, something might've changed in his life
if he'd joined the Basketball Club.
May the colors that begin to bloom on your path be beautiful.
haru no kaze ni kieta mujaki na yume
My innocent dream has vanished into the spring breeze
boku ga hitori de kanaete shimatta yo
I somehow made it come true by myself
nee
Hey
kore de ii ka na?
Is that okay?
kimi nara doushita?
How did it go for you?
How's it going? How's it going?
choushi dou desu ka?
How have you been?
kochira wa tsurai koto mo arimasu ga
Though I'm having difficult times
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
How's it going? How's it going?
motto issho ni
I hope we can
waraitakute katariaitakute
laugh and talk together again
Can you hear me?
kimi he to todoku ki ga suru kara
I believe this will reach you
koushite utatteiru yo
So I continue singing
Next time: "Sweet Sweet, Bitter."